<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="capturetype_arrays">
        <item>@string/str_document</item>
        <item>@string/str_photo</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="servertype_arrays">
        <item>@string/str_kfs_server</item>
        <item>@string/str_kta_server</item>
        <item>@string/str_kta_azure_server</item>
    </string-array>
    <color name="appbgblue">#0079C2</color>
    <color name="appbgdarkgray">#4D4D4D</color>
    <color name="appbggray">#DCDCDC</color>
    <color name="appbglightgray">#EFEFEF</color>
    <color name="apptextgray">#959595</color>
    <color name="bg_lightgray">#F0F0F0</color>
    <color name="black">#000000</color>
    <color name="blue">#0000FF</color>
    <color name="gray">#808080</color>
    <color name="light_blue">#01abeb</color>
    <color name="progressbar_color">#06de46</color>
    <color name="red">#ff0000</color>
    <color name="transparent">#00000000</color>
    <color name="white">#FFFFFF</color>
    <dimen name="activity_vertical_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="border_margin">2dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="horizontal_spacing">2dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="left_padding">8dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="right_padding">8dp</dimen>
    <string name="KMC_BC_BUSY">A read operation is already in progress.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_BUSY_DESC">You cannot call readBarcodes while a read operation is already in progress; only one outstanding read operation can be running at a time.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_IMAGE_BUFFERED">File based buffered representation is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_IMAGE_BUFFERED_DESC">Either use a stored file, or an image in memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_INVALID_IMAGE">The image contained bad image data, is null, or was otherwise invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_INVALID_IMAGE_DESC">Retake the image, or try scanning for bar codes with a different image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_BARCODE_FOUND">The image did not contain any recognizable bar codes.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_BARCODE_FOUND_DESC">Retake the image so that the barcode is complete and in focus</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_REPRESENTATION">The input image object has no active representation for File, Bitmap or both.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_REPRESENTATION_DESC">Ensure input image has an in-memory representation that is scaled down, or an un-buffered file representation before reading barcodes.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNKNOWN">There was an unknown error with the barcode reader engine.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNKNOWN_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNSUPPORTED_REGION">Selected region is not supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNSUPPORTED_REGION_DESC">Only the US region is supported for barcode string parsing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFICATION_CONFIDENCE_LOW">Classification confidence is too low to continue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFICATION_CONFIDENCE_LOW_DESC">The image used may be of poor quality, or the wrong region may have been used.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_BUSY">The image classification process is busy.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_BUSY_DESC">The image classification process is working on another request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_NOT_INITIALIZED">The image classifier is not initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_NOT_INITIALIZED_DESC">The image classification object requires the configuration and model files to be loaded before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NOT_LOADED">The classification configuration file was not loaded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NOT_LOADED_DESC">You must call the loadConfigurationFile method with a valid classification configuration file before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NULL">The classification configuration file path is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NULL_DESC">The file path for the image classification configuration file is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_BARCODE_STRING">Invalid barcode string</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_BARCODE_STRING_DESC">Please check that barcode string is not null or empty</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_IMAGE_SUPPLIED">The image used for classification is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_IMAGE_SUPPLIED_DESC">The image used for classification is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_LISTENER_NULL">The image classification listener is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_LISTENER_NULL_DESC">The object referenced to be used as a listener for the image classification completed event is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MAX_NUM_RESULTS_INVALID">The maximum number of results value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MAX_NUM_RESULTS_INVALID_DESC">Please choose a value between 1 and 64.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NOT_LOADED">The classification model file was not loaded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NOT_LOADED_DESC">You must call the loadModel method with a valid classification model file before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NULL">The classification model file path is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NULL_DESC">The file path for the image classification model file is null or empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_NO_IMAGE_SUPPLIED">No image was supplied for classification.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_NO_IMAGE_SUPPLIED_DESC">No image was supplied for classification.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_BUFFERED">Using this method such as setting a file name or reading from a file or buffer is not valid when the object is already represented by a buffered file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_BUFFERED_DESC">Set a file path or read from file after you create the image with a bitmap representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_CLEAR">"The image bitmap has already been cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_CLEAR_DESC">This warning indicates you did not need to clear the bitmap when it was already cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALTERNATE_FILEIO_ENGINE">An alternate File I/O engine was used in place of the preferred engine.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALTERNATE_FILEIO_ENGINE_DESC">The preferred File I/O engine is not compatible with the current File I/O property settings.  An alternate, compatible File I/O engine was used instead.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_IMMUTABLE">The bitmap dimensions (width, height) cannot be set because this Image object is already represented by an immutable bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_IMMUTABLE_DESC">Make sure the Image object representation is either IMAGE_REP_FILE or IMAGE_REP_UNKNOWN before attempting to specify bitmap dimensions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_NO_UPSCALE">The bitmap dimensions (width, height) cannot be set larger than the original file-based representation of this Image object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_NO_UPSCALE_DESC">Make sure the bitmap dimensions specified are smaller than those of the original file-based image representation.  Only bitmap downscaling is supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_READ_FROM_FILE_FAILED">The bitmap could not be read and decoded from the specified image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_READ_FROM_FILE_FAILED_DESC">Attempt to read and decode a bitmap from an image file failed for unknown reasons.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_WRITE_TO_FILE_FAILED">The bitmap could not be written to the specified image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_WRITE_TO_FILE_FAILED_DESC">Attempt to write a bitmap to an image file using specified MIME type and compression quality failed for unknown reasons.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER">The image object is missing a valid file buffer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFERED_READ_FAILED">Read from buffer failed because an image could not be generated from the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFERED_READ_FAILED_DESC">Free up memory or change the buffered image format and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_ALREADY_CLEARED">The file buffer has already been cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_ALREADY_CLEARED_DESC">This warning indicates you did not need to clear the file buffer when it was already cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_DESC">Write the bitmap to a file buffer before calling the read file from buffer method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_EXISTS">The file buffer for writing already exists, and the buffer contents would be lost.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_EXISTS_DESC">Make sure you clear the file buffer before writing with the same bitmap to prevent data loss.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_DELETE_BUFFERED_FILE">The file representation is a buffered file, so you cannot use delete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_DELETE_BUFFERED_FILE_DESC">Use clear buffer method to clear out the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILEPATH">The image object is missing a valid file path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILEPATH_DESC">Set the file path before calling write, read, or delete file methods.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_EXISTS">The image file path specified for writing already exists, and the file contents would be lost.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_EXISTS_DESC">Make sure you delete the file before writing with the same file name to prevent data loss.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_NOT_DELETABLE">The file specified by the image file path cannot be deleted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_NOT_DELETABLE_DESC">Specify a path to a file that your app and the OS has access rights to delete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_BITDEPTH">The OutputColor of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_BITDEPTH_DESC">Use an Image object with a compatible OutputColor.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_DPI">The DPI of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_DPI_DESC">Use an Image object with a compatible DPI.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_MIMETYPE">The mimetype setting of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_MIMETYPE_DESC">Choose a compatible mimetype setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_STILL_REMAINS">The native file delete method did not delete the file from the file system, and the file still remains.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_STILL_REMAINS_DESC">The file path may be invalid, locked or you do not have write/read access rights to delete this file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGELEAK">A bitmap already exists in the image object, therefore the read operation would create a memory leak.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGELEAK_DESC">Be sure to call imageClearBitmap before reading in a new image to avoid a memory leak.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_FILE_DIMENSIONS_ERROR">The image file dimensions (width, height) cannot be determined.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_FILE_DIMENSIONS_ERROR_DESC">There was a problem attempting to read the image dimensions from the image file path contained in the Image object.  It can be caused by an invalid file type, or unsupported compression type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_INVALID_SCALING_FACTOR">The scaling factor selected for this image object is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_INVALID_SCALING_FACTOR_DESC">The scaling factor supported for each image object is between 0.1 and 1.0.  A scaling factor of 1.0 means no scaling is performed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_IS_SCALED">The image bitmap was scaled, in order to fit in  available memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_IS_SCALED_DESC">The bitmap loaded was scaled down from its original size, in order to fit in to available memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_PERFECTION_PROFILE_EMPTY">The ImagePerfectionProfile contains no image processing operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_PERFECTION_PROFILE_EMPTY_DESC">Specify some image processing operations in the ipOperations property or ipOperationsFilePath property of the ImagePerfectionProfile.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_BITONAL">The image was written in bitonal as requested, but the image was not actually a bitonal image. The output image quality may be poor because of image conversion.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_BITONAL_DESC">Specify the correct image file output color for the image to match its contents, mimetype and file type extension.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_GRAY">The image was written in grayscale as requested, but the image was not actually a grayscale image.  The output image quality may be poor because of image conversion.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_GRAY_DESC">Specify color output for this image, using the image file output color setting to match its contents, mimetype and file type extension.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_DPI">The DPI setting is invalid for this write operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_DPI_DESC">Set a valid DPI setting before writing the file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_FOR_OBJECT_REP">This method (clear buffer or read buffer) is invalid based on the current image representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_FOR_OBJECT_REP_DESC">Make sure you use the buffer methods when the image object is in the correct state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_ISO_DATE_TIME_FORMAT">The date specified does not represent a valid ISO 8601 date/time format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_ISO_DATE_TIME_FORMAT_DESC">The date/time must correspond to the ISO 8601 international standard date/time format: YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ss.sTZD.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_JPEG_QUALITY_VALUE">The JPEG image quality value must be between 1 and 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_JPEG_QUALITY_VALUE_DESC">Specify a JPEG image quality value between 1 and 100.   Higher values indicate higher image quality but lower compression.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_JPEG_BITDEPTH">The image bits per pixel setting is invalid for a JPEG file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_JPEG_BITDEPTH_DESC">Specify an image bits per pixel setting of Grayscale or Color when writing to a JPEG file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE">The image object has an invalid mimetype setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_DESC">Set a valid mimetype before calling the write image method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_MISMATCH">The file specified by the image file path includes a file extension that does not match the mimetype.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_MISMATCH_DESC">Specify a file path and file name extension to match the mimetype, for instance a file name image.tif with a TIFF mimetype.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NOIMAGE">No bitmap in the image object is specified for writing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NOIMAGE_DESC">Specify a valid bitmap for use when writing the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_FILE">The file specified by the image file path in the image object does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_FILE_DESC">Specify a valid file path in the image object that exists in an area to which your app has access rights.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_LOAD_SETTINGS_FILE">The settings file specified in the image perfection profile does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_LOAD_SETTINGS_FILE_DESC">The settings file must be a fully qualified path to a file that exists, and contains the commands that you want to perform.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_OCR_REGION_TYPE">Region type should be set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_OCR_REGION_TYPE_DESC">Set region type to pixel of percent of the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_BUFFERED_IMAGE">There is no buffered image from which to read while the image is in this image representation, or the file representation is not FILE_BUFFERED.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_BUFFERED_IMAGE_DESC">Make sure you use the buffer methods when the image object is in the correct state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_MEMORY_FOR_BUFFERED_FILE">Could not allocate memory needed to store the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_MEMORY_FOR_BUFFERED_FILE_DESC">Free up some memory and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_BITMAP_MISMATCH">The image object bitmap is already defined, and setting the file name to an existing file violates the object contract.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_BITMAP_MISMATCH_DESC">Don\'t overwrite or change the filename in the object after it is associated with an existing bitmap for this object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_FILE_MISMATCH">The image object is already defined, and changing the bitmap violates the object contract.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_FILE_MISMATCH_DESC">Don\'t set the bitmap for the object after it already represented by a valid existing image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_MISMATCH">The object is already defined and represented, and changing to a buffered file is illegal in this state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_MISMATCH_DESC">Delete the file associated with the image, or write to a buffer after you specify the bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_NO_BITMAP">The current Image Representation does not include a bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_NO_BITMAP_DESC">The operation requested requires an Image Representation which includes a bitmap.  The Image Representation should be either IMAGE_REP_BITMAP or IMAGE_REP_BOTH.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_UNRECOGNIZED_MIME_TYPE">The Mime type of the specified image file path cannot be determined, or is unsupported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_UNRECOGNIZED_MIME_TYPE_DESC">Make sure the image file specified is one of the supported Mime types:  TIFF, JPEG, PNG.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_ENCRYPTED">Image processor detected an encryption appending issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_ENCRYPTED_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_TO_FILE">Image processor could not append to the file specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_TO_FILE_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_CHANNEL">Image processor detected an illegal channel depth specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_CHANNEL_DESC">Specify a valid channel width for this image, normally 1, 3 or 4.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_DPI">Image processor detected invalid DPI.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_DPI_DESC">Specify a valid DPI for this image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_FILE_FORMAT">Image processor detected an illegal internal file format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_FILE_FORMAT_DESC">Consult documentation for a list of valid file types.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_LINEWIDTH">Image processor detected in invalid line width.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_LINEWIDTH_DESC">Allocate memory with linewidth that is large enough for the image width and color setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_WIDTH_HEIGHT">Image processor detected invalid height or width.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_WIDTH_HEIGHT_DESC">Specify valid width and height values.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BARCODE_DRIVER">Image processor barcode driver failure.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BARCODE_DRIVER_DESC">Fatal error: no recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANCEL_OPERATION_SUCCESS">Image processor processing cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANCEL_OPERATION_SUCCESS_DESC">User has successfully aborted or cancelled image processing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANNOT_APPEND">Image processor cannot append to the file type specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANNOT_APPEND_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_EXTERNAL_PAGE">Image processor detected a bad external page.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_EXTERNAL_PAGE_DESC">Use valid external bounding tetragon points.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILEOPEN">Image processor could not open file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILEOPEN_DESC">Specify a fully qualified file path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_IO_ACCESS_BUSY">Image processor is busy for file IO access.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_IO_ACCESS_BUSY_DESC">Another thread is calling the image processor for file IO access operation. Application can either retry after certain period of time, or cancel the operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_METADATA">Image processor detected a file metadata issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_METADATA_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_READ_FAILED">Image processor detected file read error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_READ_FAILED_DESC">Fatal file read error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_HISTOGRAM">Image processor detected a bad histogram.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_HISTOGRAM_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PARM">Image processor detected an illegal parameter.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PARM_DESC">Verify your input image processing settings to make sure required parameters are correct.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PROCESSING">Image processor could not process the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PROCESSING_DESC">Take another picture with page edges included, and check your lighting, focus and orientation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_WRITE_FAILED">Image processor could not write the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_WRITE_FAILED_DESC">Fatal image write error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_HANDLE">Image processor detected a bad handle.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_HANDLE_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_POINTER">Image processor detected an illegal pointer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_POINTER_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET">Your Mobile SDK license has already been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET_DESC">Avoid setting the Mobile SDK license multiple times.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_EXPIRED">Your Mobile SDK license has expired.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_EXPIRED_DESC">Obtain a new Mobile SDK license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSING">Mobile SDK detected an invalid license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSING_DESC">Specify a valid Mobile SDK license..</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LOCK_CREATION_ERROR">EVRS could not create lock for thread safe operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LOCK_CREATION_ERROR_DESC">Failed to create system mutex used for thread safe operation. System error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_MEMORY">Image processor memory could not be allocated.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_MEMORY_DESC">Insufficient memory is available for the requested operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_METADATA_OVERFLOW">Image processor could not save the metadata in the limited output buffer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_METADATA_OVERFLOW_DESC">Specify a buffer large enough to hold the image meta data.  Free up memory and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NETWORK_READ">Image processor detected error reading from the network.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NETWORK_READ_DESC">Check your network connection.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NONEXISTANT_IMAGE">Image processor detected a nonexistent image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NONEXISTANT_IMAGE_DESC">Specify an image for processing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_BAD">Image processor detected a bad PDF file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_BAD_DESC">Fatal pdf error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_TOO_LARGE">Image processor detected the PDF file is too large to append to.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_TOO_LARGE_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PROCESS_PAGE_BUSY">Image processor is busy for page process.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PROCESS_PAGE_BUSY_DESC">Another thread is calling the image processor for page process operation. Application can either retry after certain period of time, or cancel the operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_SPEED_ACCURACY">Image processor detected a speed accuracy issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_SPEED_ACCURACY_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_UNKNOWN_FILETYPE">Image processor detected an unknown file type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_UNKNOWN_FILETYPE_DESC">Consult documentation for a list of valid file types.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_BAD_APPLICATION_CONTEXT">A valid application context was not set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_BAD_APPLICATION_CONTEXT_DESC">In order to use the Mobile SDK, you must first set a valid application context, or specify the AppContextProvider class in your application\'s Manifest.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_OBJECT_ERROR">The deserialize operation failed due to an object mismatch.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_OBJECT_ERROR_DESC">The object in the serialized file does not match the object performing the deserialize operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_VERSION_ERROR">The deserialize operation failed due to a version mismatch.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_VERSION_ERROR_DESC">The version of the serialized file is greater than the SDK version. This operation is not supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND">The referenced file or directory does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Attempt was made to read, write, or delete a non-existent file or directory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_EXCEPTION">File Not Found Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when a file specified by an application cannot be found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_ARGUMENT_EXCEPTION">Illegal Argument Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_ARGUMENT_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when a method is invoked with an argument which it can not reasonably deal with.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_THREAD_STATE_EXCEPTION">Illegal Thread State Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_THREAD_STATE_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when the attempted operation is not possible, given the state of the executing thread.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_INTERNAL_ERROR">Internal Error</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_INTERNAL_ERROR_DESC">Thrown when the Mobile SDK notices that it has gotten into an undefined state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_IO_EXCEPTION">IO Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_IO_EXCEPTION_DESC">Signals that an I/O exception of some sort has occurred. It represents the general category of exceptions produced by failed or interrupted I/O operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_NULL_POINTER_EXCEPTION">Null Pointer Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_NULL_POINTER_EXCEPTION_DESC">Attempt to access a field or method of an object or an element of an array when there is no instance or array to use.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_OUT_OF_MEMORY">The operation failed due to an out of memory condition.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_OUT_OF_MEMORY_DESC">Attempt was made to allocate memory and the native device interface indicates not enough available memory exists.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_PARAM_NEGATIVE">The operation failed due to a parameter which is less than zero.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_PARAM_NEGATIVE_DESC">The value of the parameter must be equal to or greater than zero.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_CREATE_ERROR">A session has already been created on the target Mobile SDK object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_CREATE_ERROR_DESC">You must dismiss the current session by calling sessionDismiss before creating a new session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_DISMISS_ERROR">A session has not yet been created on the target Mobile SDK object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_DISMISS_ERROR_DESC">You can only dismiss a session which was created previously.  Create a new session first by calling sessionCreate.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNKNOWN_ERROR">The operation failed due to an unknown error condition.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNKNOWN_ERROR_DESC">Unfortunately, the operation failed due to an error condition that cannot be determined.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNSUPPORTED_OPERATION">An unsupported operation was attempted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNSUPPORTED_OPERATION_DESC">Internal unsupported operation. No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_FILE_AND_BUFFERED_REPRESENTATION">File based buffered representation is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_FILE_AND_BUFFERED_REPRESENTATION_DESC">Please try another representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET">Your Mobile SDK license has already been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET_DESC">Avoid setting the Mobile SDK license multiple times.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_EXPIRED">The current date exceeds end date limit enforced by the license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_EXPIRED_DESC">Obtain a new Image Processing license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_INVALID">The string is not valid for requesting a library license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_INVALID_DESC">Specify a valid license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_PROFILE">The engine does not have any profile specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_PROFILE_DESC">You must set either a basic settings profile or an image perfection profile before calling the image processor.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_REPRESENTATION">The input image object has no active representation for File, Bitmap or both.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_REPRESENTATION_DESC">You must specify an initialized image object that refers to an image in memory or in a file, so that the image can be processed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DEVICE_REG_LICENSING_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to register the mobile device and/or obtain a license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DEVICE_REG_LICENSING_ERROR_DESC">Your mobile device either could not be registered, or failed to obtain a license. Contact your System Administrator for help in resolving this issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOMAIN">Domain invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOMAIN_DESC">Specify a valid domain.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_FIELDS_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to download document fields from the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_FIELDS_ERROR_DESC">Check  your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that document fields for the DocumentType requested are still available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_SCAN_SETTINGS_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to download scan settings.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_SCAN_SETTINGS_ERROR_DESC">Check your settings.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EMAIL">Email address invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EMAIL_DESC">For certain servers, an email address is required.  Please specify a valid email address.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EVENT_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR">Attempt to acquire a lock for the event associated with this method failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EVENT_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_IMAGE_NOT_FOUND">The image you want to remove could not be found with the imageID specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_IMAGE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Specify a valid image ID for image removal.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_DOCUMENT_TYPE_NAME">The DocumentType name specified is not valid or not available on the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_DOCUMENT_TYPE_NAME_DESC">Make sure the DocumentType name specified corresponds to a valid DocumentType on the Server. Check with your Administrator to confirm the DocumentType requested is still available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SERVER_URL">The server URL specified is invalid, or malformed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SERVER_URL_DESC">This should be a fully qualified URL, with the scheme, host name, port number, and server path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE">Unexpected user state found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_DESC">Internal unexpected error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_TRANSITION">Attempt to transition from one Session State to a subsequent Session State, where the target State is not reachable from the current State.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_TRANSITION_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_LOGIN_NOT_ALLOWED">Login not allowed in the current state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_LOGIN_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">Use server methods in the proper order.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_LOGGED_IN">You are not logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_LOGGED_IN_DESC">Use the registerDevice() and then login() methods for normal sequences.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_REGISTERED">Device not registered yet.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_REGISTERED_DESC">Use the registerDevice() method to register first.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NO_OPERATION_TO_CANCEL">There is no currently running operation to cancel.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NO_OPERATION_TO_CANCEL_DESC">You can only cancel a running operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCELLED">The currently running operation was successfully cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCELLED_DESC">The operation has been cancelled, and the SESSION_STATE has returned to the previous state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCEL_ERROR">An error occurred while attempting to cancel the running operation. The operation has been terminated.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCEL_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that the operation was successfully cancelled.  Some manual clean-up may be necessary if normal cancellation procedures did not complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_NOT_CANCELLABLE">The currently running operation cannot be cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_NOT_CANCELLABLE_DESC">You can only cancel a running operation that supports cancellation.  Check the developer guide to see what operations are cancellable.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OVERLAPPED_OPERATIONS">Overlapped session commands not allowed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OVERLAPPED_OPERATIONS_DESC">Wait until the session changed delegate is called before trying another method on the object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_IMAGE_INDEX_INVALID">The Image index specified for the current page is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_IMAGE_INDEX_INVALID_DESC">Make sure the Image index is greater than or equal to zero and less than the total number of images in this page.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_NOT_FOUND">When attempting to remove a page, that page could not be found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Specify a valid page ID for page removal.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING">Device registration already in progress.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_DESC">Wait until the registration completes before trying to register.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_NOT_ALLOWED">Registering is not allowed from this session state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should log out, and then re-register.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REQUEST_TIMEOUT">Network error: The request timed out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_DESC">Even though web services are available, there was no response to your web service request.  Contact your server administrator to ensure that it is active and available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_TIMEOUT">Server timeout is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_TIMEOUT_DESC">The value must be greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_URL_NOT_SET">The connection to the server cannot be made because the server URL has not been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_URL_NOT_SET_DESC">Set the Server URL before attempting to connect to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SESSION_STATE_BUSY">The requested operation cannot be started because the session state is transitioning as a result of an earlier request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SESSION_STATE_BUSY_DESC">Wait for the previous operation to complete, and for the session state to indicate the session state transition is complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_INVALID_JOB_ID">An invalid or missing job ID was detected while starting a document submission job.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_INVALID_JOB_ID_DESC">Ask your Administrator to confirm that your Server is configured to accept new document submission jobs.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_JOB_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to start a document submission job.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_JOB_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that your user credentials are valid.  Make sure that your device is still registered.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_BITMAP">You cannot submit a document when an image is in the IMAGE_REP_BITMAP state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_BITMAP_DESC">The image rep must be FILE or BOTH, and the FILE representation could be FILE_BUFFERED or FILE_STORED.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILEIO_ERROR">While preparing a document for submission, a file I/O error occurred reading an image file in one of the pages.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILEIO_ERROR_DESC">Make sure the image file referenced by the Image object in the Document still exists and your application has appropriate file access permissions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILE_CLOSE_ERROR">While preparing a document for submission, a file close error occurred after reading an image file in one of the pages.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILE_CLOSE_ERROR_DESC">Make sure the image file referenced by the Image object in the Document still exists and your application has appropriate file access permissions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGES_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to submit images and fields within a document to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGES_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that your user credentials are valid and that your DocumentType is recognized by the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_FILE_MISSING">The Image file indicated by the Image object in the Page cannot be found or has been deleted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_FILE_MISSING_DESC">When submitting a Document the Image objects in the Pages must reference existing Image files in the storage system.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_REP_ERROR">The Image Representation specified for one or more of the Images in the Document is not supported for submission to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_REP_ERROR_DESC">Use an Image Representation supported by the Server for each image in the Document to be submitted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_MIMETYPE_ERROR">The MIME type specified for one or more of the Images in the Document is not supported for submission to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_MIMETYPE_ERROR_DESC">Use a MIME type supported by the Server for each image in the Document to be submitted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_NO_IMAGE_ERROR">The document to be submitted contains no pages with images.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_NO_IMAGE_ERROR_DESC">Make sure each document contains at least one page with one image before submitting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_PNG">You cannot submit a document that has an image with the PNG file mime type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_PNG_DESC">Change the image object to be represented by a JPG or TIFF mime type format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_TASK_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR">Attempt to acquire a lock for the task associated with this method failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_TASK_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USERNAME_NOT_SET">Login to the server cannot be attempted because the username is blank or missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USERNAME_NOT_SET_DESC">Be sure and specify a username in the UserProfile object before attempting to login to Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_IN">An attempt was made to login to the server, even though the user is already logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_IN_DESC">You are already logged in to the Server.  Logout first, before attempting to login again with the same or different credentials.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_OUT">An attempt was made to logout from the server when the user is already logged out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_OUT_DESC">You are already logged out from the Server.  You must be logged in before logging out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_IN_ON_LOGIN">An attempt was made to login to the server when the user is already in the process of logging in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_IN_ON_LOGIN_DESC">You are already attempting  to  login to the Server.  Wait for login to complete, then logout first, before attempting to login again with the same or different credentials.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_OUT_ON_LOGOUT">An attempt was made to logout from server when the user is already in the process of logging out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_OUT_ON_LOGOUT_DESC">You are already attempting to logout from the Server when logout is already in progress.  Wait for logout to complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGIN_ERROR">An error occurred when attempting to login to the server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGIN_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that your Username and Password are valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGOUT_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to logout from the server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGOUT_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that you are successfully logged in prior to calling the logout() method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_NOT_LOGGED_IN_ON_LOGOUT">An attempt was made to logout from the server, when the user is not logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_NOT_LOGGED_IN_ON_LOGOUT_DESC">You must already be logged in to the Server before attempting to logout.</string>
    <string name="KMC_OCR_INVALID_BITMAP_SIZE">Image size selected for cropping is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_OCR_INVALID_BITMAP_SIZE_DESC">The image size should be less than original image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_SUCCESS">Success</string>
    <string name="KMC_SUCCESS_DESC">Operation Succeeded</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_ALREADY_OPEN">The camera cannot be opened, because it\'s already open.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_ALREADY_OPEN_DESC">Internal SDK error:  Camera was not released prior to re-opening.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_LOCK_ACQUIRE_FAILURE">The camera cannot be opened, because the Camera lock cannot be obtained.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_LOCK_ACQUIRE_FAILURE_DESC">Internal SDK error:  CameraManager thread was interrupted while waiting for Camera lock.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_OPERATION_FAILURE">Camera operation failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_OPERATION_FAILURE_DESC">Internal SDK error:  Camera media server died.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CREDITCARD_ARCH_NOT_SUPPORTED">Embossed credit card capture not supported on this CPU architecture.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CREDITCARD_ARCH_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_AUTO_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode AUTO is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_AUTO_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_OFF_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode OFF is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_OFF_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_ON_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode ON is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_ON_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_TORCH_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode TORCH is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_TORCH_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_COUNT">Attempted to set an invalid number of focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_COUNT_DESC">Try another value for the number of focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_EMPTY">Attempted to set a focus area with an empty or negative area.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_EMPTY_DESC">There must be at least one focus area.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_INVALID">The Rect used for the focus area is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_INVALID_DESC">Please specify a Rect that does not have zero area (e.g. is not a point, or line), for which right is greater than left, and bottom greater than top.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_NOT_SUPPORTED">Custom focus areas are not supported on this device.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Try fewer focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_IMAGE_NULL">The image sent to the image edit and review control is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_IMAGE_NULL_DESC">Please choose another image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_ASPECT_RATIO_ARGUMENT">The aspect ratio is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_ASPECT_RATIO_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value between 0 and 1</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_AXIS_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The axis threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_AXIS_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">A bad value was entered, try a valid value from 0 - 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_BORDER_THICKNESS_ARGUMENT">The border thickness is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_BORDER_THICKNESS_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 10.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_DECLINATION_ARGUMENT">The declination value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_DECLINATION_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between -180 and 180.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_HEIGHT_ARGUMENT">The height value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_HEIGHT_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PADDING_PERCENTAGE_ARGUMENT">The padding percentage is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PADDING_PERCENTAGE_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 50.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PAGE_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The page threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PAGE_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">A bad value was entered, try a valid value from 0 - 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_STABILITY_DELAY_ARGUMENT">The stability delay value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_STABILITY_DELAY_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 45.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_WIDTH_ARGUMENT">The width value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_WIDTH_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_ODE_NOT_SUPPORTED_FOR_THE_DOCUMENT_TYPE">On-Device Extraction is not supported for this type of document.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_ODE_NOT_SUPPORTED_FOR_THE_DOCUMENT_TYPE_DESC">Please try another ExtractionType.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_SCALING_FACTOR">The scaling factor should be smaller for large images.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_SCALING_FACTOR_DESC">Try another value.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_VIEW_NULL">The view passed in was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_VIEW_NULL_DESC">Please create a non-null instance of a IImageCaptureView, or pass in a non-null instance.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_BARCODE_CAPTURE">Required Bar Code Capture license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_BARCODE_CAPTURE_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_ID_EXTRACTION">Required ID extraction license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_ID_EXTRACTION_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_CAPTURE">Required Image Capture license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_CAPTURE_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_PROCESSING">Required Image Processing license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_PROCESSING_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_LOGISTICS">Required logistics license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_LOGISTICS_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_FEATURE_NOT_LICENSED">Specified license type not found in license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_FEATURE_NOT_LICENSED_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_INVALID_SERVER_RESPONSE">An invalid server response was received from the license server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_INVALID_SERVER_RESPONSE_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NETWORK_EXCEPTION">A network error occurred communicating with the license server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NETWORK_EXCEPTION_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that the specified license server name is correct.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NOT_VOLUME_LICENSE">Specified license type is not a volume license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NOT_VOLUME_LICENSE_DESC">Please specify the correct license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER">License server name was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_DESC">Please specify the correct license server name.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_TYPE">License server type was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_TYPE_DESC">Please specify the correct license server type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_TYPE">Specified license type was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_TYPE_DESC">Please specify the correct license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_OUT_OF_VOLUME_LICENSE">Operation could not be completed due to insufficient volume licenses.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_OUT_OF_VOLUME_LICENSE_DESC">Contact your administrator to obtain additional volume.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_EXPORTING">AppStats is already in the process of exporting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_EXPORTING_DESC">You should wait for the current export to complete, before starting a new one.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_RECORDING">AppStats events recording is already enabled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_RECORDING_DESC">It\'s more efficient to start recording only after it has been stopped.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_WRITING">AppStats is already in the process of writing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_WRITING_DESC">You should wait for the current write to complete, before starting a new one.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_BEGIN_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED">Beginning an AppStats session is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_BEGIN_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to start a new AppStats session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_NO_UPGRADE_PATH">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the existing version has no upgrade path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_NO_UPGRADE_PATH_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_OUT_OF_DATE">AppStats cannot be initialized because the datastore is out-of-date.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_OUT_OF_DATE_DESC">Please purge the old datastore, or use the upgradeSchema() method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_FAILED">AppStats cannot upgrade the existing datastore to the current schema.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_FAILED_DESC">Please make sure the existing datastore is one created by an earlier version of AppStats.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_MISSING_FILE">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the file does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_MISSING_FILE_DESC">Please make sure the datastore file exists before attempting to upgrade it.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_NOT_NEEDED">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the current version is up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_NOT_NEEDED_DESC">There\'s no need to upgrade a datastore which already implements the current schema.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_WRONG_STATE">Upgrade not allowed when AppStats is already initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_WRONG_STATE_DESC">AppStats must be in an uninitialized state in order to perform an upgrade.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DEVICE_ID_MISSING">User must specify device ID as a GUID or string using setDeviceID method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DEVICE_ID_MISSING_DESC">Please call setDeviceID method before init method in AppStats.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_END_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED">Ending an AppStats session is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_END_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to end an AppStats session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EVENT_THROTTLED">Elapsed time between AppStats events is less than configured throttling time.  Event not recorded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EVENT_THROTTLED_DESC">Wait until the minimum throttle time has elapsed before recording the next event.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_HANDLER_MISSING">Export handler is missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_HANDLER_MISSING_DESC">Please use the register method to pass in a handler.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_NOT_ALLOWED">Exporting from AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording and writing before attempting to export.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_FILEPATH_IS_NULL">Filepath is missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_FILEPATH_IS_NULL_DESC">The file path to datastore has not been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INIT_NOT_ALLOWED">Initializing AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INIT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording, writing, and exporting before attempting to initialize.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_JSON">Attempt to construct a malformed JSON document while exporting AppStats data.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_JSON_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_STATE_TRANSITION">Attempt to transition from one AppStats State to a subsequent AppStats State, where the target State is not reachable from the current State.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_STATE_TRANSITION_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_LOG_SESSION_EVENT_NOT_ALLOWED">Logging an AppStats session event is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_LOG_SESSION_EVENT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to log an AppStats session event.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_EXPORT">The datastore is empty: there are no AppStats event to export.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_EXPORT_DESC">Call startRecord to log some AppStats events in the datastore before attempting to export them.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_PURGE">The datastore is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_PURGE_DESC">Call startRecord to populate the datastore.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NO_SESSION_BEGUN">You must begin an AppStats session before attempting to record a session event or end a session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NO_SESSION_BEGUN_DESC">Call the beginSession method prior to calling logSessionEvent.  Call startSession prior to calling endSession.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_PURGE_NOT_ALLOWED">Purging AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_PURGE_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording, writing, and exporting before attempting to purge.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_OFF">Recording not off.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_OFF_DESC">Please stop recording using the stopRecord method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_ON">AppStats Recording not on.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_ON_DESC">Please start recording using the AppStatistics startRecord method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_AND_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED">Recording and writing AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_AND_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to record and write.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_NOT_ALLOWED">Recording AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to record.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_SESSION_ALREADY_BEGUN">You are attempting to begin a new AppStats session when one has already begun.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_SESSION_ALREADY_BEGUN_DESC">Call the endSession method prior to calling beginSession.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_STATE_BUSY">The requested operation cannot be started because the AppStats state is transitioning as a result of an earlier request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_STATE_BUSY_DESC">Wait for the previous operation to complete, before attempting to start a new operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_UNINITIALIZED">The requested operation cannot be started because the AppStats object has not been initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_UNINITIALIZED_DESC">Call the initAppStats method before attempting other AppStats operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED">Writing AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to write.</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotGetProjectZip">Could not get project zip</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotLocateVariantZip">Could not locate variant zip in project bundle</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotReadVersionTable">Could not read version table</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_IncorrectBundleVersion">Incorrect bundle version</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_NoNetworkConnection">Cannot continue; No network connection nor a local cache exists.</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_NoVariantsListedForProject">No variants listed for project \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="actionbar_lbl_screen_document_info">Field Details</string>
    <string name="actionbar_lbl_screen_preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="actionbar_lbl_screen_submit_document">Submit</string>
    <string name="app_msg_datatype_changed">Data type changed.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_docs_not_processed">There are some unprocessed images, please process them before submitting.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_image_notfound">Image not found!</string>
    <string name="app_msg_invalid_only_once_session_msg">To use the application in offline mode, the user is required  to have logged in at least once.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_invalid_session_msg">Only the last successful logged-in user will be logged in offline mode.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_offline_msg">Would you like to work in offline mode?</string>
    <string name="app_msg_offline_operaton_failed">This operation is not supported in offline mode.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_online_msg">Network is available. Would you like to login or continue using application in offline mode?</string>
    <string name="app_msg_try_again_later">Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="app_msg_value_outofrange">Current value is out of range.</string>
    <string name="app_name">KMC</string>
    <string name="app_version">2.4</string>
    <string name="balance_text">Balance</string>
    <string name="btn_label_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="btn_label_iagree">I Agree</string>
    <string name="btn_label_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_center_check">Center Check</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_center_doc">Center Document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_done">Done!</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fill_with_check">Fill viewable area\nwith check</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fill_with_doc">Fill viewable area\nwith document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fit_document">Fit Document in the frame,\nPicture will be taken automatically</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_hold_parallel">Hold Device Level</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_hold_steady">Hold Steady</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_license_user_instruction">Fill viewable area with license in QR Code format</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_move_back">Move Back</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_move_closer">Move Closer</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_no_doc_found">You may be holding the device too near to\nor too far from the Document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_rotate">Rotate Device</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_rotate_device">Incorrect Orientation - Rotate Device</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_tap_to_dismiss">Tap to dismiss</string>
    <string name="capture_giftcard">Captured photo of Gift Card</string>
    <string name="card_num_text">Card Number</string>
    <string name="card_type_text">Card Type</string>
    <string name="device_too_far_near">Document not Found.\nMove the camera to zoom in or out.</string>
    <string name="done_text">Done</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="error_lbl">Error </string>
    <string name="error_lbl_argument">Argument Error</string>
    <string name="error_lbl_download_error">Download Error</string>
    <string name="error_lbl_user_name_empty">Please enter username</string>
    <string name="error_lbl_user_not_loggedin">User Not Logged In</string>
    <string name="error_msg_do_you_want_to_logout">Logout from the server?</string>
    <string name="error_msg_doc_error">You must login first to create document.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_error_document_download">An error occurred while downloading document details.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_error_document_download_for_new_type">An error occurred while downloading details for new type.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_error_no_document_details_available">No document details available.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_error_parsing_custom_url">An error occurred parsing the custom URL</string>
    <string name="error_msg_giftcard_balance">Could not get the balance.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_provided_url_has_errors">The provided URL has errors and is not usable.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_query_string_has_errors_and_is_not_usable">The query string has errors and is not usable</string>
    <string name="error_msg_submit_failed">Submit failed.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_while_logging_in">User login error.</string>
    <string name="error_msg_while_registering">Error while registering </string>
    <string name="exp_date_text">Expiry Date</string>
    <string name="gallery_permission_alert">You need to allow access to Gallery. To allow, goto Settings->Apps->Capture->Permissions and change the permissions to Allow</string>
    <string name="giftcardbalance_title">Gift Card Balance</string>
    <string name="giftcardlist_text">Select from the supported cards below to capture an image of your gift card.</string>
    <string name="giftcardlist_title">Gift Cards</string>
    <string name="hdr_terms_conditions">Terms And Conditions</string>
    <string name="hold_steady_message">Hold steady</string>
    <string name="img_review_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="img_review_retake">Retake</string>
    <string name="improper_orientation">Improper Device Orientation</string>
    <string name="launch_name">Capture</string>
    <string name="lbl_and">and</string>
    <string name="lbl_blurry">blurry</string>
    <string name="lbl_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="lbl_connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="lbl_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="lbl_document">Document</string>
    <string name="lbl_document_name">Name</string>
    <string name="lbl_done">Done</string>
    <string name="lbl_image">Image is </string>
    <string name="lbl_images">Images</string>
    <string name="lbl_invalid_email">Invalid email</string>
    <string name="lbl_login">Login</string>
    <string name="lbl_login_error">Login Error</string>
    <string name="lbl_login_failed_error">Login Error</string>
    <string name="lbl_logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="lbl_no_email_registered">No Email registered</string>
    <string name="lbl_not_blurry">\tnot blurry</string>
    <string name="lbl_offline">Offline</string>
    <string name="lbl_oversaturated">too bright.</string>
    <string name="lbl_sample_date">31 Jan 2015  | 10:17AM</string>
    <string name="lbl_selected">Selected</string>
    <string name="lbl_submit_not_initiated">Submit not initiated</string>
    <string name="lbl_total_images">Total Images</string>
    <string name="lbl_total_pages">Total Pages</string>
    <string name="lbl_undersaturated">too dark.</string>
    <string name="move_closer">Move camera closer to the document</string>
    <string name="msg_range">range</string>
    <string name="msg_to">to</string>
    <string name="permission_alert">Application may misbehave,Please goto Settings->Apps->Capture->Permissions and change the permissions to Allow</string>
    <string name="permissions">PERMISSIONS</string>
    <string name="pin_text">Card Pin</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_caneling">Canceling</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_downloading_doc_details">Downloading details. Please wait</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_downloading_image">Fetching image. Please wait</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_logging_in">Logging in</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_logging_out">Logging out</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_please_enter_values_between">Please enter values between </string>
    <string name="progress_msg_please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_processing">Processing</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_registering_device">Registering device</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_required_fields_empty">Required fields cannot be empty.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_session_already_has_active_case_open">A Kofax Mobile Capture (KMC) is currently not on Home screen. Please navigate back to the KMC Home screen or exit application completely.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_session_already_running_use_back_to_exit">A Kofax Mobile Capture (KMC) session is already running.\nPlease use back key to exit KMC before changing login credentials.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_session_currently_busy">A Kofax Mobile Capture session is currently busy.\nPlease try again after session is free.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_session_currently_logging_in">A Kofax Mobile Capture (KMC) session is currently logging in.\nPlease wait for KMC to complete the login process before starting a new session.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_session_currently_paused">A Kofax Mobile Capture (KMC) session is currently paused and waiting to log in.\nPlease bring this KMC session to the foreground (tap on KMC icon), and wait for login to complete.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_submitting">Submitting</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_updating_list">Updating list. Please wait</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_updating_list_failed">List update failed. Please check network.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_updating_list_label">Updating list</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_updating_view">Updating view. Please wait</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_url_contains_assistkofx_document_type">"Assist Kofax Documnet type is not supported in custom URL."</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_url_contains_invalid_document_types">URL contains invalid document type.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_url_contains_invalid_parameters">URL contains invalid parameters.</string>
    <string name="progress_msg_validating_fields">Validating fields. Please wait</string>
    <string name="refresh_text">Refresh</string>
    <string name="server_validation_message">Please enter valid server url</string>
    <string name="str_KB">KB</string>
    <string name="str_MB">MB</string>
    <string name="str_about_kmc">About KMC</string>
    <string name="str_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="str_account_info">Account Information</string>
    <string name="str_add">Add</string>
    <string name="str_add_desc">Add the image.</string>
    <string name="str_add_images">Add Images</string>
    <string name="str_advanced_options">Advanced Options</string>
    <string name="str_anonymous">Anonymous Login</string>
    <string name="str_app_homepage">Kofax, Inc. Home Page</string>
    <string name="str_app_homepage_link">www.kofax.com</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_Kofax_Support_Commitment"><b> Kofax Support Commitment </b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_arg">END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_arg_text"><b>IMPORTANT NOTICE: By downloading or installing any Kofax Software Products to Your (or your employers) computer(s) or network, You are agreeing to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Software License Agreement. If You are downloading or installing Kofax Software in connection with your employment by a business or other entity you represent or work for, you are further representing to Kofax that You are authorized and agree to bind such business or entity to this Agreement in connection with downloading , installing or using any Kofax Software Product (in which case the term You as used in this Agreement refers to such business or entity. Use of Kofax Software Products may further require a license key or product registration.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text1">  Kofax, Inc. ("Kofax") grants to You a limited, non-exclusive license right (the License) to install and use the downloaded Kofax Software Product(s) (the Software). The License allows You to use the Software in object code form only for the purposes (internal use, evaluation, testing, demonstration, disaster recovery), duration and extent for which You have paid the appropriate license fees, as evidenced by one or more valid and mutually agreed upon purchase order documents between You and Kofax or an authorized Kofax reseller identifying the product(s) licensed (the Software) and any applicable limitations on use (such as volume limitations or concurrent client module use limitations). Where Your License is limited on an annual volume basis, Your authorized volume usage limit shall pertain to the 12 month period commencing from the date the Software is delivered to You. The License includes the right to use the Software in connection with providing document handling services on behalf of clients as a business process outsourcer or service bureau. Any features or functionality to be included in any future or subsequent releases of the Software are at the sole discretion of Kofax and nothing in this Agreement should be interpreted or construed to include any right on Your part to receive any specific features or functionality in the future.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text10">  UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL KOFAX BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOST PROFITS, LOST OR DEGRADED DATA, INTERRUPTION OF BUSINESS, PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS, OR FOR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, HOWEVER CAUSED AND REGARDLESS OF THEORY OF LIABILITY, ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF (OR INABILITY TO USE) THE SOFTWARE OR THE PROVISION OF SERVICES HEREUNDER, EVEN IF KOFAX HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text10_1"> Except as set forth in Section 9, Kofaxs liability to you will in no event, whether in contract, tort (including negligence) or otherwise, exceed the fees You actually paid to Kofax pursuant to this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text11">  You agree that a material breach of this Agreement adversely affecting Kofaxs proprietary rights in the Software or other confidential materials provided hereunder would cause irreparable injury to Kofax for which monetary damages would not be an adequate remedy and, therefore, that Kofax shall be entitled to equitable relief (e.g. injunction) in addition to any remedies it may have hereunder or at law.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text12">  You may not assign this Agreement or any of the rights granted hereunder without the prior written approval of Kofax.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text13">  All notices under this Agreement shall be in writing, shall reference this Agreement, and shall be deemed given: 1) when delivered personally; 2) when sent by confirmed facsimile transmission; 3) five days after having been sent by registered or certified mail, return receipt requested; or 4) one day after deposit with a commercial overnight carrier, with written verification of receipt.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text14">  Failure by either of us to enforce any provision of this Agreement shall not be deemed a waiver of future enforcement of that or any other provision. Similarly, the provision of any accommodation exceeding the requirements of this Agreement shall not constitute a waiver of any provision hereof, nor shall it be construed to establish a course of dealing contrary to the express terms hereof. If any provision of this Agreement shall be adjudged by a court of competent jurisdiction to be unenforceable, that provision shall be limited or eliminated to the minimum extent necessary so that this Agreement shall otherwise remain in full force and effect.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text15">  In the event of any dispute arising out of or relating to this Agreement, we shall attempt in good faith to resolve such dispute through informal means, including timely escalation of the dispute to senior management having full settlement authority. If the dispute is not resolved as a result of these efforts, the matter will be submitted to final and binding arbitration under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. We agree to cooperate in selecting an arbitrator and in scheduling the arbitration proceedings. Arbitration proceedings will be conducted by one arbitrator in the English language, applying the substantive state and federal laws of and for California, excluding its laws pertaining to conflict of law. We specifically agree that that body of law known as the United Nations Convention on the International Sale of Goods shall not apply to this Agreement. The site of any proceedings shall be Orange County, California. The provisions of this section and any resulting award may be enforced by any court of competent jurisdiction. The prevailing party in any arbitration shall be entitled to an award of all costs, fees and reasonable expenses, including attorneys fees, incurred as a result of the arbitration or any action to enforce the arbitration award. Punitive damages may not be awarded in connection with any arbitration proceeding arising out of or relating to this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text16">  Neither party to this Agreement shall be liable for non-performance to the extent that such non-performance is caused by events or conditions beyond that partys control, provided such party promptly notifies the other thereof and makes reasonable efforts to perform.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text17">  Notwithstanding the terms and conditions of this Agreement, some portions of the Software that constitute third party software, including software provided under a public license, (Third Party Software) may be licensed to you subject to additional and/or different terms and conditions.  In such event, the software license agreements accompany such Third Party Software or are set forth in the thirdpartylicenses.txt file accompanying the  Software.  Unless explicitly stated in such software license agreements, the use of the Third Party Software will be governed exclusively by the terms and conditions thereof.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text18">  This Agreement, including all attachments, constitutes the entire agreement between the parties with respect to the subject matter hereof. It supersedes and replaces all prior or contemporaneous understandings or agreements, written or oral, regarding such subject matter, and it shall supersede any and all conflicting provisions of any order document(s) between the parties. This Agreement may be modified, amended or waived only by a written instrument signed by duly authorized representatives of both parties.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text2">  The License shall remain in effect perpetually unless terminated in accordance with the terms of this Agreement. You may terminate this Agreement and the License at any time by certifying destruction of all copies of the Software and associated documentation. This Agreement will further terminate upon Your failure to cure any material breach of this Agreement within 30 days of written notice from Kofax regarding such breach. In the event of termination, regardless of cause, the License will immediately terminate, and you will promptly destroy all copies of the Software. Sections 6, 7, and 10-17 of this Agreement, and the obligations embodied therein, will survive any termination of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text3">  Kofax or an authorized Kofax reseller will provide support services for which You have paid the required annual support fees, subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement and the </string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text3_1"> (the Support Commitment), the current version of which are available at all times at www.Kofax.com/support/ and which is incorporated herein by reference. What is included and excluded from the services, and other requirements, is described in the Support Commitment. Kofax may make minor revisions to the Support Commitment from time to time without notice to You. Support pricing shall be as quoted and agreed upon between the Parties for the initial term, and shall increase for renewal terms by an amount not to exceed 5% of the prior year term fee, provided that increases associated with additional software license purchases, if any, shall be incorporated into the base for the purpose of calculation of each annual increase. The initial one year support services term will begin on the first day of the month following the invoice date of the Software. For as long as Kofax makes support services for the Software generally available to all of its customers, this Agreement will automatically renew on each anniversary date thereafter for a new one year term, unless You give Kofax 60 days written notice, prior to the end of the current term, of Your intent not to renew. Kofax will invoice You for renewal fees up to 60 days prior to expiration of each term. Kofax may terminate and suspend performance of all support services if You fail to pay any past due Kofax invoice within 10 days of written notice of such failure, in the event of any other material breach by You which remains uncured 30 days after notice thereof or if any of the Software ceases to be subject of a valid Software License Agreement. Kofax will not provide support following expiration of this Agreement. In the event You desire support to be reinstated following expiration, You agree: 1) to pay a reinstatement fee   equal to the current annual support fee and any unpaid support fees from the date of expiration to the date of reinstatement; and 2) to pay for at least one additional year of support services from the date of reinstatement. All software maintenance releases, updates, patches, workarounds or other software and/or documentation furnished to You pursuant to this Agreement shall be deemed to be Software, as that term is used herein. Upon receipt and installation of a software maintenance release to a Software program, You may keep (in addition to the current revision archival copy permitted hereunder) one copy of the previous version of that Software for archival purposes only and shall destroy all other copies of the previous version.  </string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text4">  All professional services engagements shall be performed under a separate professional services agreement, mutually agreed upon in writing by authorized representatives of each of us. Any fees for Software hereunder shall be due and payable under the terms set forth in Section 5 of this Agreement, and shall not be dependent or contingent in any way upon the performance or completion of any separate professional services engagement.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text5">  All rights granted in this Agreement are conditional upon payment of the appropriate fees. Invoices are due and payable 30 days from date of invoice. You agree to pay or reimburse all sales, use, VAT or excise taxes, duties or assessments arising on or measured by amounts payable to Kofax hereunder. You are not responsible for Kofaxs income taxes.  All tangibles will be delivered FOB Kofaxs offices.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text6">  The Software is proprietary commercial software developed at private expense by Kofax and/or its licensors.  Kofax reserves all intellectual property rights to the Software and its documentation under U.S. Copyright Law and international copyright treaty provisions as well as trade secret, industrial property, unfair competition or similar laws applicable to the locality where you use it. No product or service provided under this Agreement will be deemed a work-made-for-hire. In accordance with copyright law You may not, and You may not allow any third party to, 1) decompile, disassemble, or otherwise reverse engineer or attempt to reconstruct or discover any source code or underlying ideas of the Software by any means  whatsoever; 2) remove any product identification, copyright legend or other notices; 3) rent, lease, lend, or sublicense the Software to third parties; 4) modify, incorporate into or with other software or create a derivative work of any part of the Software except as specified in the user documentation or as permitted under separate license agreement with Kofax; or 5) attempt to use the Software, or any portion thereof, in excess of its licensed capacity. Except as may be reasonably required to use the Software in accordance with the License, and except as strictly required for back-up and archival purposes, You may not copy the Software or any portion thereof.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text7">  Subject to the limitations stated herein, Kofax warrants to You, the original end user, that, for a period of 90 days from the date of receipt a) the hardware key and the media on which Software is furnished will be free of defects in materials and workmanship, and b) such Software, as delivered, will materially conform to Kofaxs then-current documentation for such Software. Your exclusive remedy, and Kofaxs entire liability, under this warranty will be, at Kofaxs option, the replacement of the non-conforming Software, hardware key, media and/or documentation or a refund of the license fee You paid, subject to Your return of the Software. This Limited Warranty is void if failure of the Software has resulted from accident, abuse or misapplication. Any replacement Software will be warranted for the remainder of the original warranty period or 30 days, whichever is longer. The services provided hereunder shall be performed in a good and workmanlike manner in accordance with generally accepted standards of the software industry. This section does not apply to the provision of professional services.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text8">  THE EXPRESS WARRANTY ABOVE IS IN LIEU OF ALL OTHER WARRANTIES. KOFAX DISCLAIMS ALL OTHER WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING ANY WARRANTY OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE; OR ANY WARRANTY ARISING FROM THE COURSE OF DEALING BETWEEN THE PARTIES OR FROM TRADE USAGE.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text9">  Kofax will defend, at its own expense, any claim, suit or proceeding brought against you to the extent it is based upon a claim that Your use of the Software in the United States, Canada, Australia or the European Union pursuant to this Agreement infringes upon any patent, copyright or trade secret of a third party. You agree that you will promptly notify Kofax in writing of any such claim or action and give Kofax full information and assistance in connection therewith. Kofax will have the sole right to control the defense of, and to settle or compromise, any such claim or action. If You comply with the provisions hereof, Kofax will pay all damages, costs and expenses finally awarded to third parties against You in such action. If the Software is, or in Kofaxs opinion might be, held to infringe as set forth above, Kofax may, at its option, replace or modify the Software so as to avoid infringement, or procure the right for You to continue to use the Software. If neither of such alternatives is, in Kofaxs opinion, commercially reasonable, You will return the infringing Software to Kofax, and Kofax\'s sole liability, in addition to its obligation to pay awarded damages, costs and expenses as set forth above, shall be to refund the license fees You paid to Kofax hereunder, depreciated on a 3-year, straight-line basis.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text9_1">Kofax will have no liability for any claim of infringement arising as a result of a) Your use of the Software in combination with any items not supplied by Kofax; b) any modification of the Software at Your request; c) use of other than the latest revision of the Software if use of the latest revision would avoid the infringement; or d) use outside the scope of the granted licenses.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_text9_2">The foregoing states Kofaxs entire liability concerning infringement of intellectual property rights, including but not limited to, patent, copyright and trade secret rights.</string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title1"><b>1. Software License.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title10"><b>10.  Limitation of Liability.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title11"><b>11.  Equitable Remedies.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title12"><b>12.  Assignment.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title13"><b>13.  Notices.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title14"><b>14.  Waiver/Severability.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title15"><b>15.  Resolution of Disputes.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title16"><b>16.  Force Majeure.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title17"><b>17. Third Party Software.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title18"><b>18.  Complete Agreement.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title2"><b>2. Term "&amp;" Termination.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title3"><b>3. Support Services.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title4"><b>4. Professional Services Engagements.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title5"><b>5. Price-Payment-Delivery.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title6"><b>6. Copyright.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title7"><b>7. Limited Warranty.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title8"><b>8. Disclaimer of Additional Warranties.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_license_title9"><b>9.  Intellectual Property Indemnification.</b></string>
    <string name="str_app_patents">Patents Pending</string>
    <string name="str_app_patents_text">Use is subject to license terms. \n\nThird party software is copyrighted and licensed from Kofax\'s suppliers. \n\nKofax, the Kofax logo, and the Kofax product names stated herein are trademarks or registered trademarks of Kofax in the U.S. and other countries. All other trademarks are the trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective owners.</string>
    <string name="str_app_privicy"> Privacy Statement\n 2016 Kofax, Inc. All rights reserved.</string>
    <string name="str_app_sdk_version">KMC SDK Version</string>
    <string name="str_app_techsupport">Kofax Technical Support</string>
    <string name="str_app_techsupport_link">www.kofax.com/support</string>
    <string name="str_app_version">Version</string>
    <string name="str_auto">Auto</string>
    <string name="str_capture_time_memory_warning">There is no enough space in device to capture another document. Please create more free space in device.</string>
    <string name="str_change_item_type">Change item type</string>
    <string name="str_change_item_type_desc">Change the item type from item type to another item type.</string>
    <string name="str_change_type">Change Type</string>
    <string name="str_confirm_dont_show_this_message_again">Don\'t show this message again</string>
    <string name="str_created">Created</string>
    <string name="str_crop">Crop</string>
    <string name="str_crop_desc">Manually crop the image.</string>
    <string name="str_datatype_not_matching">"Data type not matching for field "</string>
    <string name="str_date">Date</string>
    <string name="str_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="str_delete_desc">Delete images from any items.</string>
    <string name="str_delete_images">Delete Images</string>
    <string name="str_dimension">Dimension</string>
    <string name="str_docs">Documents</string>
    <string name="str_document">Document</string>
    <string name="str_domain">Domain</string>
    <string name="str_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="str_edit_info">Edit information</string>
    <string name="str_edit_information">Edit Information</string>
    <string name="str_edit_item_info">Edit item info</string>
    <string name="str_edit_item_info_desc">Modify or enter field data associated with an item.</string>
    <string name="str_email">Email</string>
    <string name="str_empty"/>
    <string name="str_enter_manually">Enter manually</string>
    <string name="str_existing_item">Existing item</string>
    <string name="str_existing_item_desc">Created new document and not submitted to server, this item will be in existing document list. Submit them whenever intended.</string>
    <string name="str_flash">Flash</string>
    <string name="str_help">Help</string>
    <string name="str_help_info">Help Info</string>
    <string name="str_help_info_cap">HELP INFO</string>
    <string name="str_image_details">Image Details</string>
    <string name="str_image_feedback">Image Feedback</string>
    <string name="str_image_process">Show Processed Image</string>
    <string name="str_image_unprocess">Show Original Image</string>
    <string name="str_info">Info</string>
    <string name="str_kfs_server">Kofax Front Office Server</string>
    <string name="str_kmc_url">www.kofax.com/mobilecapture</string>
    <string name="str_kta_azure_server">Kofax TotalAgility Azure</string>
    <string name="str_kta_server">Kofax TotalAgility</string>
    <string name="str_latitude">Latitude</string>
    <string name="str_launch_time_memory_warning">Your device is low on memory. Please free up some space in  the device and restart this app.</string>
    <string name="str_license_agreement">License Agreement</string>
    <string name="str_longitude">Longitude</string>
    <string name="str_manual_capture">Manual Capture</string>
    <string name="str_manual_capture_time">Manual Capture Time(Sec)</string>
    <string name="str_mobile_capture">KOFAX MOBILE CAPTURE</string>
    <string name="str_more">More</string>
    <string name="str_more_about_kmc">To know more about KMC click this link below</string>
    <string name="str_motion_sensitivity">Motion Sensitivity</string>
    <string name="str_msg_do_you_want_to_import_existing_data">Do you want to import existing data?</string>
    <string name="str_new_item">New item</string>
    <string name="str_new_item_desc">Choose from a list of item types and a start a new item.</string>
    <string name="str_nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="str_no_documents">No recent data</string>
    <string name="str_no_fields">No fields</string>
    <string name="str_no_internet_connection_available">Offline Mode</string>
    <string name="str_not_available">Not available</string>
    <string name="str_off">Off</string>
    <string name="str_on">On</string>
    <string name="str_password">Password</string>
    <string name="str_photo">Photo</string>
    <string name="str_pic_from_device_camera">Picture was taken by camera</string>
    <string name="str_pic_from_gallery">Picture was selected from gallery</string>
    <string name="str_port">Port</string>
    <string name="str_preview_image">Preview Image</string>
    <string name="str_process">Process</string>
    <string name="str_process_all_images">Processing parameters have been updated on server. \nPlease process all the images again.</string>
    <string name="str_processing_all_images">Processing parameters have been updated on server. \nReprocessing all the images with updated parameters.</string>
    <string name="str_retake">Retake</string>
    <string name="str_revert">Revert</string>
    <string name="str_revert_desc">Revert images.</string>
    <string name="str_revert_images">Revert Images</string>
    <string name="str_rotate">Rotate</string>
    <string name="str_rotate_desc">Rotate images.</string>
    <string name="str_save">Save</string>
    <string name="str_select">Select</string>
    <string name="str_server_host_name">Server Hostname</string>
    <string name="str_server_type">Server Type</string>
    <string name="str_servers">Servers</string>
    <string name="str_size">Size</string>
    <string name="str_ssl">SSL</string>
    <string name="str_submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="str_submit_item">Submit item</string>
    <string name="str_submit_item_desc">Submit captured item images to server.</string>
    <string name="str_submit_server">Submit to Server</string>
    <string name="str_to">to</string>
    <string name="str_url">URL</string>
    <string name="str_use_kofax_server">Use Kofax Server</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_change_document_type_before_using_option">Please change document type before using any option.</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_change_item_type_confirmation">Changing the document type will reprocess images and reset existing field information.\n\nDo you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_change_item_type_confirmation_title">Change Type</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_change_item_type_lowend_confirmation">Changing the document type will remove all the processed images and reset existing field information.\n\nDo you want to continue?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_delete_confirmation_title">Delete</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_delete_image_confirmation">Do you want to delete the image?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_delete_selected_images_confirmation">Do you want to delete selected images?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_delete_single_selected_image_confirmation">Do you want to delete selected image?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_generic_delete_confirmation">Do you want to delete?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_no_image_selected">No images selected</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_no_image_to_select">Add one or more images to select</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_no_item_type_exists">Selected document type is no longer available on server.</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_revert_confirmation_title">Revert</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_revert_selected_images_confirmation">Do you want to revert selected images?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_revert_single_image_confirmation">Do you want to revert the image?</string>
    <string name="str_user_msg_revert_single_selected_image_confirmation">Do you want to revert selected image?</string>
    <string name="str_user_name">Username</string>
    <string name="tap_on_image">Tap on the above image to retake</string>
    <string name="title_help_kofax">Assist Kofax</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Pending</string>
    <string name="toast_app_work_offline">Application will work in offline mode.</string>
    <string name="toast_balance_retrieval_failed">Balance retrieval failed</string>
    <string name="toast_cardnumber_required">Card number cannot be empty to request balance.</string>
    <string name="toast_empty_document">There are no images to be submitted.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_bitmap_null">Error: bitmap is null.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_cannot_initiate_submit">Submit cannot be initiated.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_cannot_retrieve_image_details">Cannot retrieve image details.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_cannot_submit">Cannot submit.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_email_required">An email address is required to be registered before using application.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_field_details_cannot_be_downloaded">Field details cannot be downloaded.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_image_processing_cannot_be_performed">Image processing cannot be performed.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_invalid_email">Please enter valid email address.</string>
    <string name="toast_error_required_fields_empty">One or more required fields are empty.\nPlease fill in the required details.</string>
    <string name="toast_exception_read_license_file">IO exception occurred while reading file.</string>
    <string name="toast_failed_to_write_field_info">Failed to write field information.</string>
    <string name="toast_fields_added">New Fields Are Added.</string>
    <string name="toast_fields_removed">Fields Are Removed.</string>
    <string name="toast_item_submitted_successful">Submit successful.</string>
    <string name="toast_no_fields">Selected document has no fields.</string>
    <string name="toast_no_network_connectivity">No network available.</string>
    <string name="toast_processing_failed">Image processing failed.</string>
    <string name="toast_processing_params_changed">Processing parameters for the selected item have changed. Reprocessing all images using new processing parameters.</string>
    <string name="toast_save_image_failed">Failed to save the image.</string>
    <string name="toast_session_state_busy">Session state is currently busy.\nPlease try again later.</string>
    <string name="toast_try_again">Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="toast_unable_to_cancel_operation">Unable to cancel the operation.</string>
    <string name="toast_unable_to_decode_file">Unable to decode file</string>
    <string name="toast_unrecoverable_problem">Unrecoverable problem, trying to login again.</string>
    <string name="toast_use_valid_license">Please use valid KFS license to proceed</string>
    <string name="userInstruction">"Fit document in the frame.\nPicture will be taken automatically"</string>
    <string name="userbpInstruction">"Fill viewable area with payment coupon"</string>
    <string name="usercdInstruction">"Fill viewable area with check</string>
    <string name="userdlInstruction">"Fill viewable area with ID card"</string>
    <string name="usergiftcardInstruction">"Fill viewable area with gift card"</string>
    <string name="userppInstruction">"Fill viewable area with Passport"</string>
    <style name="AppBaseTheme" parent="android:Theme.Light">
        <!--
            Theme customizations available in newer API levels can go in
            res/values-vXX/styles.xml, while customizations related to
            backward-compatibility can go here.
        -->

    </style>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="AppBaseTheme">

        <!-- All customizations that are NOT specific to a particular API-level can go here. -->
        <item name="android:actionBarStyle">@style/MyActionBar</item>
        <item name="android:actionBarTabTextStyle">@style/MyActionBarTabText</item>
        <item name="android:actionModeBackground">@color/white</item>
        <item name="android:actionMenuTextColor">@color/black</item>
        <item name="android:titleTextStyle">@style/MyActionBarTitleTextStyle</item>
    </style>
    <style name="MyActionBar" parent="@android:style/Widget.Holo.Light.ActionBar.Solid.Inverse">
        <item name="android:background">@drawable/actionbar_bg</item>
    </style>
    <style name="MyActionBarTabText" parent="android:style/Widget.Holo.ActionBar.TabText">
        <item name="android:textColor">@color/black</item>
        <item name="android:textStyle">bold</item>
        <!-- item name="android:textAllCaps">false</item -->
    </style>
    <style name="MyActionBarTitleTextStyle" parent="android:style/TextAppearance.Holo.Widget.ActionBar.Title">
        <item name="android:textStyle">bold</item>
        <!-- item name="android:textAllCaps">false</item -->
    </style>
</resources>