<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="KMC_BC_BUSY">A read operation is already in progress.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_BUSY_DESC">You cannot call readBarcodes while a read operation is already in progress; only one outstanding read operation can be running at a time.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_IMAGE_BUFFERED">File based buffered representation is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_IMAGE_BUFFERED_DESC">Either use a stored file, or an image in memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_INVALID_IMAGE">The image contained bad image data, is null, or was otherwise invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_INVALID_IMAGE_DESC">Retake the image, or try scanning for bar codes with a different image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_BARCODE_FOUND">The image did not contain any recognizable bar codes.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_BARCODE_FOUND_DESC">Retake the image so that the barcode is complete and in focus</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_REPRESENTATION">The input image object has no active representation for File, Bitmap or both.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_NO_REPRESENTATION_DESC">Ensure input image has an in-memory representation that is scaled down, or an un-buffered file representation before reading barcodes.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNKNOWN">There was an unknown error with the barcode reader engine.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNKNOWN_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNSUPPORTED_REGION">Selected region is not supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_BC_UNSUPPORTED_REGION_DESC">Only the US region is supported for barcode string parsing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFICATION_CONFIDENCE_LOW">Classification confidence is too low to continue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFICATION_CONFIDENCE_LOW_DESC">The image used may be of poor quality, or the wrong region may have been used.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_BUSY">The image classification process is busy.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_BUSY_DESC">The image classification process is working on another request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_NOT_INITIALIZED">The image classifier is not initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CLASSIFIER_NOT_INITIALIZED_DESC">The image classification object requires the configuration and model files to be loaded before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NOT_LOADED">The classification configuration file was not loaded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NOT_LOADED_DESC">You must call the loadConfigurationFile method with a valid classification configuration file before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NULL">The classification configuration file path is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_CONFIG_NULL_DESC">The file path for the image classification configuration file is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_BARCODE_STRING">Invalid barcode string</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_BARCODE_STRING_DESC">Please check that barcode string is not null or empty</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_IMAGE_SUPPLIED">The image used for classification is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_INVALID_IMAGE_SUPPLIED_DESC">The image used for classification is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_LISTENER_NULL">The image classification listener is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_LISTENER_NULL_DESC">The object referenced to be used as a listener for the image classification completed event is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MAX_NUM_RESULTS_INVALID">The maximum number of results value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MAX_NUM_RESULTS_INVALID_DESC">Please choose a value between 1 and 64.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NOT_LOADED">The classification model file was not loaded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NOT_LOADED_DESC">You must call the loadModel method with a valid classification model file before an image can be classified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NULL">The classification model file path is null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_MODEL_NULL_DESC">The file path for the image classification model file is null or empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_NO_IMAGE_SUPPLIED">No image was supplied for classification.</string>
    <string name="KMC_CL_NO_IMAGE_SUPPLIED_DESC">No image was supplied for classification.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_BUFFERED">Using this method such as setting a file name or reading from a file or buffer is not valid when the object is already represented by a buffered file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_BUFFERED_DESC">Set a file path or read from file after you create the image with a bitmap representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_CLEAR">"The image bitmap has already been cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALREADY_CLEAR_DESC">This warning indicates you did not need to clear the bitmap when it was already cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALTERNATE_FILEIO_ENGINE">An alternate File I/O engine was used in place of the preferred engine.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_ALTERNATE_FILEIO_ENGINE_DESC">The preferred File I/O engine is not compatible with the current File I/O property settings.  An alternate, compatible File I/O engine was used instead.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_IMMUTABLE">The bitmap dimensions (width, height) cannot be set because this Image object is already represented by an immutable bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_IMMUTABLE_DESC">Make sure the Image object representation is either IMAGE_REP_FILE or IMAGE_REP_UNKNOWN before attempting to specify bitmap dimensions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_NO_UPSCALE">The bitmap dimensions (width, height) cannot be set larger than the original file-based representation of this Image object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_DIMENSIONS_NO_UPSCALE_DESC">Make sure the bitmap dimensions specified are smaller than those of the original file-based image representation.  Only bitmap downscaling is supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_READ_FROM_FILE_FAILED">The bitmap could not be read and decoded from the specified image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_READ_FROM_FILE_FAILED_DESC">Attempt to read and decode a bitmap from an image file failed for unknown reasons.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_WRITE_TO_FILE_FAILED">The bitmap could not be written to the specified image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BITMAP_WRITE_TO_FILE_FAILED_DESC">Attempt to write a bitmap to an image file using specified MIME type and compression quality failed for unknown reasons.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER">The image object is missing a valid file buffer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFERED_READ_FAILED">Read from buffer failed because an image could not be generated from the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFERED_READ_FAILED_DESC">Free up memory or change the buffered image format and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_ALREADY_CLEARED">The file buffer has already been cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_ALREADY_CLEARED_DESC">This warning indicates you did not need to clear the file buffer when it was already cleared.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_DESC">Write the bitmap to a file buffer before calling the read file from buffer method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_EXISTS">The file buffer for writing already exists, and the buffer contents would be lost.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_BUFFER_EXISTS_DESC">Make sure you clear the file buffer before writing with the same bitmap to prevent data loss.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_DELETE_BUFFERED_FILE">The file representation is a buffered file, so you cannot use delete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_DELETE_BUFFERED_FILE_DESC">Use clear buffer method to clear out the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILEPATH">The image object is missing a valid file path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILEPATH_DESC">Set the file path before calling write, read, or delete file methods.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_EXISTS">The image file path specified for writing already exists, and the file contents would be lost.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_EXISTS_DESC">Make sure you delete the file before writing with the same file name to prevent data loss.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_NOT_DELETABLE">The file specified by the image file path cannot be deleted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_NOT_DELETABLE_DESC">Specify a path to a file that your app and the OS has access rights to delete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_BITDEPTH">The OutputColor of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_BITDEPTH_DESC">Use an Image object with a compatible OutputColor.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_DPI">The DPI of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_DPI_DESC">Use an Image object with a compatible DPI.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_MIMETYPE">The mimetype setting of the Image object is not compatible with the specified financial services industry output TIFF file restriction.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_RESTRICTION_MIMETYPE_DESC">Choose a compatible mimetype setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_STILL_REMAINS">The native file delete method did not delete the file from the file system, and the file still remains.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_FILE_STILL_REMAINS_DESC">The file path may be invalid, locked or you do not have write/read access rights to delete this file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGELEAK">A bitmap already exists in the image object, therefore the read operation would create a memory leak.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGELEAK_DESC">Be sure to call imageClearBitmap before reading in a new image to avoid a memory leak.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_FILE_DIMENSIONS_ERROR">The image file dimensions (width, height) cannot be determined.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_FILE_DIMENSIONS_ERROR_DESC">There was a problem attempting to read the image dimensions from the image file path contained in the Image object.  It can be caused by an invalid file type, or unsupported compression type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_INVALID_SCALING_FACTOR">The scaling factor selected for this image object is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_INVALID_SCALING_FACTOR_DESC">The scaling factor supported for each image object is between 0.1 and 1.0.  A scaling factor of 1.0 means no scaling is performed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_IS_SCALED">The image bitmap was scaled, in order to fit in  available memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_IS_SCALED_DESC">The bitmap loaded was scaled down from its original size, in order to fit in to available memory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_PERFECTION_PROFILE_EMPTY">The ImagePerfectionProfile contains no image processing operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_PERFECTION_PROFILE_EMPTY_DESC">Specify some image processing operations in the ipOperations property or ipOperationsFilePath property of the ImagePerfectionProfile.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_BITONAL">The image was written in bitonal as requested, but the image was not actually a bitonal image. The output image quality may be poor because of image conversion.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_BITONAL_DESC">Specify the correct image file output color for the image to match its contents, mimetype and file type extension.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_GRAY">The image was written in grayscale as requested, but the image was not actually a grayscale image.  The output image quality may be poor because of image conversion.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_IMAGE_WRITTEN_IS_NOT_GRAY_DESC">Specify color output for this image, using the image file output color setting to match its contents, mimetype and file type extension.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_DPI">The DPI setting is invalid for this write operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_DPI_DESC">Set a valid DPI setting before writing the file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_FOR_OBJECT_REP">This method (clear buffer or read buffer) is invalid based on the current image representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_FOR_OBJECT_REP_DESC">Make sure you use the buffer methods when the image object is in the correct state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_ISO_DATE_TIME_FORMAT">The date specified does not represent a valid ISO 8601 date/time format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_ISO_DATE_TIME_FORMAT_DESC">The date/time must correspond to the ISO 8601 international standard date/time format: YYYY-MM-DDThh:mm:ss.sTZD.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_JPEG_QUALITY_VALUE">The JPEG image quality value must be between 1 and 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_INVALID_JPEG_QUALITY_VALUE_DESC">Specify a JPEG image quality value between 1 and 100.   Higher values indicate higher image quality but lower compression.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_JPEG_BITDEPTH">The image bits per pixel setting is invalid for a JPEG file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_JPEG_BITDEPTH_DESC">Specify an image bits per pixel setting of Grayscale or Color when writing to a JPEG file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE">The image object has an invalid mimetype setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_DESC">Set a valid mimetype before calling the write image method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_MISMATCH">The file specified by the image file path includes a file extension that does not match the mimetype.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_MIMETYPE_MISMATCH_DESC">Specify a file path and file name extension to match the mimetype, for instance a file name image.tif with a TIFF mimetype.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NOIMAGE">No bitmap in the image object is specified for writing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NOIMAGE_DESC">Specify a valid bitmap for use when writing the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_FILE">The file specified by the image file path in the image object does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_FILE_DESC">Specify a valid file path in the image object that exists in an area to which your app has access rights.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_LOAD_SETTINGS_FILE">The settings file specified in the image perfection profile does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_LOAD_SETTINGS_FILE_DESC">The settings file must be a fully qualified path to a file that exists, and contains the commands that you want to perform.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_OCR_REGION_TYPE">Region type should be set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NONEXISTENT_OCR_REGION_TYPE_DESC">Set region type to pixel of percent of the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_BUFFERED_IMAGE">There is no buffered image from which to read while the image is in this image representation, or the file representation is not FILE_BUFFERED.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_BUFFERED_IMAGE_DESC">Make sure you use the buffer methods when the image object is in the correct state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_MEMORY_FOR_BUFFERED_FILE">Could not allocate memory needed to store the buffered file image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_NO_MEMORY_FOR_BUFFERED_FILE_DESC">Free up some memory and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_BITMAP_MISMATCH">The image object bitmap is already defined, and setting the file name to an existing file violates the object contract.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_BITMAP_MISMATCH_DESC">Don\'t overwrite or change the filename in the object after it is associated with an existing bitmap for this object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_FILE_MISMATCH">The image object is already defined, and changing the bitmap violates the object contract.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_FILE_MISMATCH_DESC">Don\'t set the bitmap for the object after it already represented by a valid existing image file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_MISMATCH">The object is already defined and represented, and changing to a buffered file is illegal in this state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_MISMATCH_DESC">Delete the file associated with the image, or write to a buffer after you specify the bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_NO_BITMAP">The current Image Representation does not include a bitmap.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_OBJECT_REP_NO_BITMAP_DESC">The operation requested requires an Image Representation which includes a bitmap.  The Image Representation should be either IMAGE_REP_BITMAP or IMAGE_REP_BOTH.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_UNRECOGNIZED_MIME_TYPE">The Mime type of the specified image file path cannot be determined, or is unsupported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_ED_UNRECOGNIZED_MIME_TYPE_DESC">Make sure the image file specified is one of the supported Mime types:  TIFF, JPEG, PNG.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_ENCRYPTED">Image processor detected an encryption appending issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_ENCRYPTED_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_TO_FILE">Image processor could not append to the file specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_APPEND_TO_FILE_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_CHANNEL">Image processor detected an illegal channel depth specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_CHANNEL_DESC">Specify a valid channel width for this image, normally 1, 3 or 4.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_DPI">Image processor detected invalid DPI.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_DPI_DESC">Specify a valid DPI for this image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_FILE_FORMAT">Image processor detected an illegal internal file format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_FILE_FORMAT_DESC">Consult documentation for a list of valid file types.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_LINEWIDTH">Image processor detected in invalid line width.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_LINEWIDTH_DESC">Allocate memory with linewidth that is large enough for the image width and color setting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_WIDTH_HEIGHT">Image processor detected invalid height or width.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BAD_WIDTH_HEIGHT_DESC">Specify valid width and height values.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BARCODE_DRIVER">Image processor barcode driver failure.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_BARCODE_DRIVER_DESC">Fatal error: no recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANCEL_OPERATION_SUCCESS">Image processor processing cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANCEL_OPERATION_SUCCESS_DESC">User has successfully aborted or cancelled image processing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANNOT_APPEND">Image processor cannot append to the file type specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_CANNOT_APPEND_DESC">Fatal append error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_EXTERNAL_PAGE">Image processor detected a bad external page.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_EXTERNAL_PAGE_DESC">Use valid external bounding tetragon points.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILEOPEN">Image processor could not open file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILEOPEN_DESC">Specify a fully qualified file path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_IO_ACCESS_BUSY">Image processor is busy for file IO access.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_IO_ACCESS_BUSY_DESC">Another thread is calling the image processor for file IO access operation. Application can either retry after certain period of time, or cancel the operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_METADATA">Image processor detected a file metadata issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_METADATA_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_READ_FAILED">Image processor detected file read error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_FILE_READ_FAILED_DESC">Fatal file read error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_HISTOGRAM">Image processor detected a bad histogram.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_HISTOGRAM_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PARM">Image processor detected an illegal parameter.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PARM_DESC">Verify your input image processing settings to make sure required parameters are correct.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PROCESSING">Image processor could not process the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_PROCESSING_DESC">Take another picture with page edges included, and check your lighting, focus and orientation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_WRITE_FAILED">Image processor could not write the image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_IMAGE_WRITE_FAILED_DESC">Fatal image write error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_HANDLE">Image processor detected a bad handle.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_HANDLE_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_POINTER">Image processor detected an illegal pointer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_INVALID_POINTER_DESC">Fatal error: No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET">Your Mobile SDK license has already been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET_DESC">Avoid setting the Mobile SDK license multiple times.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_EXPIRED">Your Mobile SDK license has expired.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSE_EXPIRED_DESC">Obtain a new Mobile SDK license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSING">Mobile SDK detected an invalid license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LICENSING_DESC">Specify a valid Mobile SDK license..</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LOCK_CREATION_ERROR">EVRS could not create lock for thread safe operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_LOCK_CREATION_ERROR_DESC">Failed to create system mutex used for thread safe operation. System error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_MEMORY">Image processor memory could not be allocated.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_MEMORY_DESC">Insufficient memory is available for the requested operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_METADATA_OVERFLOW">Image processor could not save the metadata in the limited output buffer.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_METADATA_OVERFLOW_DESC">Specify a buffer large enough to hold the image meta data.  Free up memory and retry.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NETWORK_READ">Image processor detected error reading from the network.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NETWORK_READ_DESC">Check your network connection.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NONEXISTANT_IMAGE">Image processor detected a nonexistent image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_NONEXISTANT_IMAGE_DESC">Specify an image for processing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_BAD">Image processor detected a bad PDF file.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_BAD_DESC">Fatal pdf error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_TOO_LARGE">Image processor detected the PDF file is too large to append to.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PDF_TOO_LARGE_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PROCESS_PAGE_BUSY">Image processor is busy for page process.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_PROCESS_PAGE_BUSY_DESC">Another thread is calling the image processor for page process operation. Application can either retry after certain period of time, or cancel the operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_SPEED_ACCURACY">Image processor detected a speed accuracy issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_SPEED_ACCURACY_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_UNKNOWN_FILETYPE">Image processor detected an unknown file type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_EV_UNKNOWN_FILETYPE_DESC">Consult documentation for a list of valid file types.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_BAD_APPLICATION_CONTEXT">A valid application context was not set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_BAD_APPLICATION_CONTEXT_DESC">In order to use the Mobile SDK, you must first set a valid application context, or specify the AppContextProvider class in your application\'s Manifest.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_OBJECT_ERROR">The deserialize operation failed due to an object mismatch.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_OBJECT_ERROR_DESC">The object in the serialized file does not match the object performing the deserialize operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_VERSION_ERROR">The deserialize operation failed due to a version mismatch.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_DESERIALIZE_VERSION_ERROR_DESC">The version of the serialized file is greater than the SDK version. This operation is not supported.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND">The referenced file or directory does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Attempt was made to read, write, or delete a non-existent file or directory.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_EXCEPTION">File Not Found Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_FILE_NOT_FOUND_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when a file specified by an application cannot be found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_ARGUMENT_EXCEPTION">Illegal Argument Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_ARGUMENT_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when a method is invoked with an argument which it can not reasonably deal with.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_THREAD_STATE_EXCEPTION">Illegal Thread State Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_ILLEGAL_THREAD_STATE_EXCEPTION_DESC">Thrown when the attempted operation is not possible, given the state of the executing thread.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_INTERNAL_ERROR">Internal Error</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_INTERNAL_ERROR_DESC">Thrown when the Mobile SDK notices that it has gotten into an undefined state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_IO_EXCEPTION">IO Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_IO_EXCEPTION_DESC">Signals that an I/O exception of some sort has occurred. It represents the general category of exceptions produced by failed or interrupted I/O operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_NULL_POINTER_EXCEPTION">Null Pointer Exception</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_NULL_POINTER_EXCEPTION_DESC">Attempt to access a field or method of an object or an element of an array when there is no instance or array to use.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_OUT_OF_MEMORY">The operation failed due to an out of memory condition.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_OUT_OF_MEMORY_DESC">Attempt was made to allocate memory and the native device interface indicates not enough available memory exists.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_PARAM_NEGATIVE">The operation failed due to a parameter which is less than zero.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_PARAM_NEGATIVE_DESC">The value of the parameter must be equal to or greater than zero.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_CREATE_ERROR">A session has already been created on the target Mobile SDK object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_CREATE_ERROR_DESC">You must dismiss the current session by calling sessionDismiss before creating a new session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_DISMISS_ERROR">A session has not yet been created on the target Mobile SDK object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_SESSION_DISMISS_ERROR_DESC">You can only dismiss a session which was created previously.  Create a new session first by calling sessionCreate.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNKNOWN_ERROR">The operation failed due to an unknown error condition.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNKNOWN_ERROR_DESC">Unfortunately, the operation failed due to an error condition that cannot be determined.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNSUPPORTED_OPERATION">An unsupported operation was attempted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_GN_UNSUPPORTED_OPERATION_DESC">Internal unsupported operation. No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_FILE_AND_BUFFERED_REPRESENTATION">File based buffered representation is not valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_FILE_AND_BUFFERED_REPRESENTATION_DESC">Please try another representation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET">Your Mobile SDK license has already been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_ALREADY_SET_DESC">Avoid setting the Mobile SDK license multiple times.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_EXPIRED">The current date exceeds end date limit enforced by the license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_EXPIRED_DESC">Obtain a new Image Processing license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_INVALID">The string is not valid for requesting a library license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_LICENSE_INVALID_DESC">Specify a valid license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_PROFILE">The engine does not have any profile specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_PROFILE_DESC">You must set either a basic settings profile or an image perfection profile before calling the image processor.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_REPRESENTATION">The input image object has no active representation for File, Bitmap or both.</string>
    <string name="KMC_IP_NO_REPRESENTATION_DESC">You must specify an initialized image object that refers to an image in memory or in a file, so that the image can be processed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DEVICE_REG_LICENSING_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to register the mobile device and/or obtain a license.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DEVICE_REG_LICENSING_ERROR_DESC">Your mobile device either could not be registered, or failed to obtain a license. Contact your System Administrator for help in resolving this issue.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOMAIN">Domain invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOMAIN_DESC">Specify a valid domain.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_FIELDS_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to download document fields from the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_FIELDS_ERROR_DESC">Check  your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that document fields for the DocumentType requested are still available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_SCAN_SETTINGS_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to download scan settings.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_DOWNLOAD_DOCUMENT_SCAN_SETTINGS_ERROR_DESC">Check your settings.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EMAIL">Email address invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EMAIL_DESC">For certain servers, an email address is required.  Please specify a valid email address.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EVENT_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR">Attempt to acquire a lock for the event associated with this method failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_EVENT_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_IMAGE_NOT_FOUND">The image you want to remove could not be found with the imageID specified.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_IMAGE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Specify a valid image ID for image removal.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_DOCUMENT_TYPE_NAME">The DocumentType name specified is not valid or not available on the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_DOCUMENT_TYPE_NAME_DESC">Make sure the DocumentType name specified corresponds to a valid DocumentType on the Server. Check with your Administrator to confirm the DocumentType requested is still available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SERVER_URL">The server URL specified is invalid, or malformed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SERVER_URL_DESC">This should be a fully qualified URL, with the scheme, host name, port number, and server path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE">Unexpected user state found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_DESC">Internal unexpected error.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_TRANSITION">Attempt to transition from one Session State to a subsequent Session State, where the target State is not reachable from the current State.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_INVALID_SESSION_STATE_TRANSITION_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_LOGIN_NOT_ALLOWED">Login not allowed in the current state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_LOGIN_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">Use server methods in the proper order.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_LOGGED_IN">You are not logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_LOGGED_IN_DESC">Use the registerDevice() and then login() methods for normal sequences.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_REGISTERED">Device not registered yet.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NOT_REGISTERED_DESC">Use the registerDevice() method to register first.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NO_OPERATION_TO_CANCEL">There is no currently running operation to cancel.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_NO_OPERATION_TO_CANCEL_DESC">You can only cancel a running operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCELLED">The currently running operation was successfully cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCELLED_DESC">The operation has been cancelled, and the SESSION_STATE has returned to the previous state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCEL_ERROR">An error occurred while attempting to cancel the running operation. The operation has been terminated.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_CANCEL_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that the operation was successfully cancelled.  Some manual clean-up may be necessary if normal cancellation procedures did not complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_NOT_CANCELLABLE">The currently running operation cannot be cancelled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OPERATION_NOT_CANCELLABLE_DESC">You can only cancel a running operation that supports cancellation.  Check the developer guide to see what operations are cancellable.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OVERLAPPED_OPERATIONS">Overlapped session commands not allowed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_OVERLAPPED_OPERATIONS_DESC">Wait until the session changed delegate is called before trying another method on the object.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_IMAGE_INDEX_INVALID">The Image index specified for the current page is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_IMAGE_INDEX_INVALID_DESC">Make sure the Image index is greater than or equal to zero and less than the total number of images in this page.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_NOT_FOUND">When attempting to remove a page, that page could not be found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_PAGE_NOT_FOUND_DESC">Specify a valid page ID for page removal.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING">Device registration already in progress.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_DESC">Wait until the registration completes before trying to register.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_NOT_ALLOWED">Registering is not allowed from this session state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REGISTERING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should log out, and then re-register.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REQUEST_TIMEOUT">Network error: The request timed out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_REQUEST_TIMEOUT_DESC">Even though web services are available, there was no response to your web service request.  Contact your server administrator to ensure that it is active and available.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_TIMEOUT">Server timeout is incorrect.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_TIMEOUT_DESC">The value must be greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_URL_NOT_SET">The connection to the server cannot be made because the server URL has not been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SERVER_URL_NOT_SET_DESC">Set the Server URL before attempting to connect to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SESSION_STATE_BUSY">The requested operation cannot be started because the session state is transitioning as a result of an earlier request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SESSION_STATE_BUSY_DESC">Wait for the previous operation to complete, and for the session state to indicate the session state transition is complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_INVALID_JOB_ID">An invalid or missing job ID was detected while starting a document submission job.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_INVALID_JOB_ID_DESC">Ask your Administrator to confirm that your Server is configured to accept new document submission jobs.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_JOB_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to start a document submission job.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_START_SUBMIT_JOB_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that your user credentials are valid.  Make sure that your device is still registered.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_BITMAP">You cannot submit a document when an image is in the IMAGE_REP_BITMAP state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_BITMAP_DESC">The image rep must be FILE or BOTH, and the FILE representation could be FILE_BUFFERED or FILE_STORED.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILEIO_ERROR">While preparing a document for submission, a file I/O error occurred reading an image file in one of the pages.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILEIO_ERROR_DESC">Make sure the image file referenced by the Image object in the Document still exists and your application has appropriate file access permissions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILE_CLOSE_ERROR">While preparing a document for submission, a file close error occurred after reading an image file in one of the pages.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_FILE_CLOSE_ERROR_DESC">Make sure the image file referenced by the Image object in the Document still exists and your application has appropriate file access permissions.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGES_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to submit images and fields within a document to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGES_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection and ask your Administrator to confirm that your user credentials are valid and that your DocumentType is recognized by the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_FILE_MISSING">The Image file indicated by the Image object in the Page cannot be found or has been deleted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_FILE_MISSING_DESC">When submitting a Document the Image objects in the Pages must reference existing Image files in the storage system.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_REP_ERROR">The Image Representation specified for one or more of the Images in the Document is not supported for submission to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_IMAGE_REP_ERROR_DESC">Use an Image Representation supported by the Server for each image in the Document to be submitted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_MIMETYPE_ERROR">The MIME type specified for one or more of the Images in the Document is not supported for submission to the Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_MIMETYPE_ERROR_DESC">Use a MIME type supported by the Server for each image in the Document to be submitted.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_NO_IMAGE_ERROR">The document to be submitted contains no pages with images.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_DOCUMENT_NO_IMAGE_ERROR_DESC">Make sure each document contains at least one page with one image before submitting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_PNG">You cannot submit a document that has an image with the PNG file mime type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_SUBMIT_PNG_DESC">Change the image object to be represented by a JPG or TIFF mime type format.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_TASK_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR">Attempt to acquire a lock for the task associated with this method failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_TASK_LOCK_ACQUIRE_ERROR_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USERNAME_NOT_SET">Login to the server cannot be attempted because the username is blank or missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USERNAME_NOT_SET_DESC">Be sure and specify a username in the UserProfile object before attempting to login to Server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_IN">An attempt was made to login to the server, even though the user is already logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_IN_DESC">You are already logged in to the Server.  Logout first, before attempting to login again with the same or different credentials.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_OUT">An attempt was made to logout from the server when the user is already logged out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_ALREADY_LOGGED_OUT_DESC">You are already logged out from the Server.  You must be logged in before logging out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_IN_ON_LOGIN">An attempt was made to login to the server when the user is already in the process of logging in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_IN_ON_LOGIN_DESC">You are already attempting  to  login to the Server.  Wait for login to complete, then logout first, before attempting to login again with the same or different credentials.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_OUT_ON_LOGOUT">An attempt was made to logout from server when the user is already in the process of logging out.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGGING_OUT_ON_LOGOUT_DESC">You are already attempting to logout from the Server when logout is already in progress.  Wait for logout to complete.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGIN_ERROR">An error occurred when attempting to login to the server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGIN_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that your Username and Password are valid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGOUT_ERROR">An error occurred attempting to logout from the server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_LOGOUT_ERROR_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that you are successfully logged in prior to calling the logout() method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_NOT_LOGGED_IN_ON_LOGOUT">An attempt was made to logout from the server, when the user is not logged in.</string>
    <string name="KMC_LO_USER_NOT_LOGGED_IN_ON_LOGOUT_DESC">You must already be logged in to the Server before attempting to logout.</string>
    <string name="KMC_OCR_INVALID_BITMAP_SIZE">Image size selected for cropping is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_OCR_INVALID_BITMAP_SIZE_DESC">The image size should be less than original image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_SUCCESS">Success</string>
    <string name="KMC_SUCCESS_DESC">Operation Succeeded</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_ALREADY_OPEN">The camera cannot be opened, because it\'s already open.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_ALREADY_OPEN_DESC">Internal SDK error:  Camera was not released prior to re-opening.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_LOCK_ACQUIRE_FAILURE">The camera cannot be opened, because the Camera lock cannot be obtained.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_LOCK_ACQUIRE_FAILURE_DESC">Internal SDK error:  CameraManager thread was interrupted while waiting for Camera lock.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_OPERATION_FAILURE">Camera operation failed.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CAMERA_OPERATION_FAILURE_DESC">Internal SDK error:  Camera media server died.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CREDITCARD_ARCH_NOT_SUPPORTED">Embossed credit card capture not supported on this CPU architecture.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_CREDITCARD_ARCH_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_AUTO_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode AUTO is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_AUTO_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_OFF_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode OFF is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_OFF_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_ON_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode ON is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_ON_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_TORCH_NOT_SUPPORTED">Flash mode TORCH is not supported with the camera hardware.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FLASH_TORCH_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Choose a different flash mode.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_COUNT">Attempted to set an invalid number of focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_COUNT_DESC">Try another value for the number of focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_EMPTY">Attempted to set a focus area with an empty or negative area.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_EMPTY_DESC">There must be at least one focus area.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_INVALID">The Rect used for the focus area is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_INVALID_DESC">Please specify a Rect that does not have zero area (e.g. is not a point, or line), for which right is greater than left, and bottom greater than top.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_NOT_SUPPORTED">Custom focus areas are not supported on this device.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_FOCUS_AREA_NOT_SUPPORTED_DESC">Try fewer focus areas.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_IMAGE_NULL">The image sent to the image edit and review control is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_IMAGE_NULL_DESC">Please choose another image.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_ASPECT_RATIO_ARGUMENT">The aspect ratio is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_ASPECT_RATIO_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value between 0 and 1</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_AXIS_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The axis threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_AXIS_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">A bad value was entered, try a valid value from 0 - 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_BORDER_THICKNESS_ARGUMENT">The border thickness is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_BORDER_THICKNESS_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 10.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_DECLINATION_ARGUMENT">The declination value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_DECLINATION_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between -180 and 180.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_HEIGHT_ARGUMENT">The height value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_HEIGHT_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PADDING_PERCENTAGE_ARGUMENT">The padding percentage is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PADDING_PERCENTAGE_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 50.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PAGE_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The page threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_PAGE_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">A bad value was entered, try a valid value from 0 - 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_STABILITY_DELAY_ARGUMENT">The stability delay value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_STABILITY_DELAY_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 100.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT">The threshold value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_THRESHOLD_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a value between 0 and 45.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_WIDTH_ARGUMENT">The width value is invalid.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_INVALID_WIDTH_ARGUMENT_DESC">Please choose a positive value greater than 0.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_ODE_NOT_SUPPORTED_FOR_THE_DOCUMENT_TYPE">On-Device Extraction is not supported for this type of document.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_ODE_NOT_SUPPORTED_FOR_THE_DOCUMENT_TYPE_DESC">Please try another ExtractionType.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_SCALING_FACTOR">The scaling factor should be smaller for large images.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_SCALING_FACTOR_DESC">Try another value.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_VIEW_NULL">The view passed in was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UI_VIEW_NULL_DESC">Please create a non-null instance of a IImageCaptureView, or pass in a non-null instance.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_BARCODE_CAPTURE">Required Bar Code Capture license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_BARCODE_CAPTURE_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_ID_EXTRACTION">Required ID extraction license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_ID_EXTRACTION_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_CAPTURE">Required Image Capture license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_CAPTURE_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_PROCESSING">Required Image Processing license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_IMAGE_PROCESSING_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_LOGISTICS">Required logistics license not found.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSE_LOGISTICS_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_FEATURE_NOT_LICENSED">Specified license type not found in license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_FEATURE_NOT_LICENSED_DESC">Please make sure the application is using the correct license string.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_INVALID_SERVER_RESPONSE">An invalid server response was received from the license server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_INVALID_SERVER_RESPONSE_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NETWORK_EXCEPTION">A network error occurred communicating with the license server.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NETWORK_EXCEPTION_DESC">Check your network connection, and make sure that the specified license server name is correct.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NOT_VOLUME_LICENSE">Specified license type is not a volume license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NOT_VOLUME_LICENSE_DESC">Please specify the correct license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER">License server name was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_DESC">Please specify the correct license server name.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_TYPE">License server type was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_SERVER_TYPE_DESC">Please specify the correct license server type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_TYPE">Specified license type was null.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_LICENSING_NULL_LICENSE_TYPE_DESC">Please specify the correct license type.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_OUT_OF_VOLUME_LICENSE">Operation could not be completed due to insufficient volume licenses.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_OUT_OF_VOLUME_LICENSE_DESC">Contact your administrator to obtain additional volume.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_EXPORTING">AppStats is already in the process of exporting.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_EXPORTING_DESC">You should wait for the current export to complete, before starting a new one.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_RECORDING">AppStats events recording is already enabled.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_RECORDING_DESC">It\'s more efficient to start recording only after it has been stopped.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_WRITING">AppStats is already in the process of writing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_ALREADY_WRITING_DESC">You should wait for the current write to complete, before starting a new one.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_BEGIN_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED">Beginning an AppStats session is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_BEGIN_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to start a new AppStats session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_NO_UPGRADE_PATH">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the existing version has no upgrade path.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_NO_UPGRADE_PATH_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_OUT_OF_DATE">AppStats cannot be initialized because the datastore is out-of-date.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_OUT_OF_DATE_DESC">Please purge the old datastore, or use the upgradeSchema() method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_FAILED">AppStats cannot upgrade the existing datastore to the current schema.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_FAILED_DESC">Please make sure the existing datastore is one created by an earlier version of AppStats.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_MISSING_FILE">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the file does not exist.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_MISSING_FILE_DESC">Please make sure the datastore file exists before attempting to upgrade it.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_NOT_NEEDED">AppStats cannot upgrade the datastore because the current version is up-to-date.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_NOT_NEEDED_DESC">There\'s no need to upgrade a datastore which already implements the current schema.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_WRONG_STATE">Upgrade not allowed when AppStats is already initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DATASTORE_UPGRADE_WRONG_STATE_DESC">AppStats must be in an uninitialized state in order to perform an upgrade.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DEVICE_ID_MISSING">User must specify device ID as a GUID or string using setDeviceID method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_DEVICE_ID_MISSING_DESC">Please call setDeviceID method before init method in AppStats.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_END_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED">Ending an AppStats session is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_END_SESSION_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to end an AppStats session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EVENT_THROTTLED">Elapsed time between AppStats events is less than configured throttling time.  Event not recorded.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EVENT_THROTTLED_DESC">Wait until the minimum throttle time has elapsed before recording the next event.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_HANDLER_MISSING">Export handler is missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_HANDLER_MISSING_DESC">Please use the register method to pass in a handler.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_NOT_ALLOWED">Exporting from AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_EXPORT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording and writing before attempting to export.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_FILEPATH_IS_NULL">Filepath is missing.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_FILEPATH_IS_NULL_DESC">The file path to datastore has not been set.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INIT_NOT_ALLOWED">Initializing AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INIT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording, writing, and exporting before attempting to initialize.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_JSON">Attempt to construct a malformed JSON document while exporting AppStats data.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_JSON_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_STATE_TRANSITION">Attempt to transition from one AppStats State to a subsequent AppStats State, where the target State is not reachable from the current State.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_INVALID_STATE_TRANSITION_DESC">Internal unexpected error.  No recommendation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_LOG_SESSION_EVENT_NOT_ALLOWED">Logging an AppStats session event is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_LOG_SESSION_EVENT_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You must start recording first in order to log an AppStats session event.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_EXPORT">The datastore is empty: there are no AppStats event to export.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_EXPORT_DESC">Call startRecord to log some AppStats events in the datastore before attempting to export them.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_PURGE">The datastore is empty.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NOTHING_TO_PURGE_DESC">Call startRecord to populate the datastore.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NO_SESSION_BEGUN">You must begin an AppStats session before attempting to record a session event or end a session.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_NO_SESSION_BEGUN_DESC">Call the beginSession method prior to calling logSessionEvent.  Call startSession prior to calling endSession.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_PURGE_NOT_ALLOWED">Purging AppStatistics is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_PURGE_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop recording, writing, and exporting before attempting to purge.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_OFF">Recording not off.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_OFF_DESC">Please stop recording using the stopRecord method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_ON">AppStats Recording not on.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORDING_NOT_ON_DESC">Please start recording using the AppStatistics startRecord method.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_AND_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED">Recording and writing AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_AND_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to record and write.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_NOT_ALLOWED">Recording AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_RECORD_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to record.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_SESSION_ALREADY_BEGUN">You are attempting to begin a new AppStats session when one has already begun.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_SESSION_ALREADY_BEGUN_DESC">Call the endSession method prior to calling beginSession.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_STATE_BUSY">The requested operation cannot be started because the AppStats state is transitioning as a result of an earlier request.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_STATE_BUSY_DESC">Wait for the previous operation to complete, before attempting to start a new operation.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_UNINITIALIZED">The requested operation cannot be started because the AppStats object has not been initialized.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_UNINITIALIZED_DESC">Call the initAppStats method before attempting other AppStats operations.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED">Writing AppStats events is not allowed from this AppStats state.</string>
    <string name="KMC_UT_STATS_WRITING_NOT_ALLOWED_DESC">You should stop exporting before attempting to write.</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotGetProjectZip">Could not get project zip</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotLocateVariantZip">Could not locate variant zip in project bundle</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_CouldNotReadVersionTable">Could not read version table</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_IncorrectBundleVersion">Incorrect bundle version</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_NoNetworkConnection">Cannot continue; No network connection nor a local cache exists.</string>
    <string name="ProjectProvider_NoVariantsListedForProject">No variants listed for project \'%s\'</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_center_check">Center Check</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_center_doc">Center Document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_done">Done!</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fill_with_check">Fill viewable area\nwith check</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fill_with_doc">Fill viewable area\nwith document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_fit_document">Fit Document in the frame,\nPicture will be taken automatically</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_hold_parallel">Hold Device Level</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_hold_steady">Hold Steady</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_license_user_instruction">Fill viewable area with license in QR Code format</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_move_back">Move Back</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_move_closer">Move Closer</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_no_doc_found">You may be holding the device too near to\nor too far from the Document</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_rotate">Rotate Device</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_rotate_device">Incorrect Orientation - Rotate Device</string>
    <string name="cap_guide_tap_to_dismiss">Tap to dismiss</string>
    <string name="img_review_accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="img_review_retake">Retake</string>
</resources>